Oh, my God.
Hey, everybody!
How are you doing on this wonderful Sunday?
Today is Easter Day, I think.
It is today, I believe.
Which is a perfect day to start a new game.
The day to start Terraria, or Terraria.
I don't know how to pronounce that, but I'm sure you'll let me know.
Man, I'm excited.
It's always exciting to start something new.
Bayor33, welcome!
You have become a potato now.
Thank you so much, man.
I hope everyone is doing great.
Okay, so, what is there to say?
I know almost nothing about this game, except that it's similar to Minecraft, but in 2D.
That's about my extent of knowledge.
And yeah.
Isanti, thank you for the five euros.
Let's go!
Very excited for this?
Me too.
It's going to be exciting.
I haven't even looked through the settings yet, actually.
Let me just ask you real quick.
How is the audio levels?
Because, hopefully the audio is going to be the same in the game as it is in the menu.
I hope it's okay.
You can hear me clearly.
The game is not too loud.
Minecraft is 3D Terraria, nice.
Audio is good.
Nice.
I'm going to ask again about the audio in like 30 minutes after we've been playing for
a bit.
Also, I put the chat there because I'm not sure where there's going to be UI elements.
So hopefully it's fine.
Michael B, thank you for the five pounds, man.
Godspeed.
Thank you.
I shall need it on this journey into the unknown, into the land of Terraria.
We shall be doing some mining and some crafting and fighting, I guess.
It's the name of the game.
So I think it's time for me to just close you guys down, no offense, and jump into the
game.
I'm liking this music, by the way.
It gets me pumped.
It's a nice menu music.
Okay, hold on.
I need to minimize here to minimize you.
There.
All right.
Good luck, everybody.
See you on the other side.
Well, in 30 minutes, I'm going to ask for audio at that point.
Let me actually quickly look in the settings.
Video.
I just want everything on max.
Oh, there is even parallax frames.
I don't know what that means.
Okay.
Whatever.
Doesn't seem like there's any graphics options.
That's okay.
Single player.
New.
Okay.
We get to choose a woman or a man.
I guess I'll be a man.
What is this?
Oh, that's the head.
But what the fuck is this image right here?
This I don't understand.
But okay.
I'm going to try and pick the hair that matches mine in real life.
Let's see.
Oh, there's more.
Oh, there's so many hairstyles.
What the heck?
This is me in real life?
No, not really.
Maybe this is good.
I don't like customization too much, actually.
You guys know that by now, probably.
Sure, that's fine.
What is this?
Oh, skin color, I guess.
Armor.
Oh, okay.
Sure.
Uh...
That's fine.
Name.
Oliver.
Submit.
I shall submit to the game that my name is indeed Oliver.
What's this?
Difficulty, I guess.
Journey characters start with extra equipment, can only be played on journey worlds.
Classic characters drop money on death.
Medium core characters drop items on death.
And hardcore characters die for good.
Oh, shit.
I don't know, man.
If you want to go Minecraft style, it's got to be medium core, I guess.
But the question is, do I want to play Minecraft style?
Classic makes it sound like that's how it's supposed to be played, doesn't it?
Journey is a little bit weird.
I wonder if this is like an online thing.
Journey worlds, you know.
Like servers or whatever.
I'm going to go with classic, I guess, sure.
And what now? Oh, I can select.
Classic.
Weird.
Play.
Favorite.
Rename.
Oh, okay, I see.
I made a character.
Play.
Go!
Wait, what?
What just happened?
Oh, select world.
Oh, I get it.
The unwicked armpit.
The enduring niche of ogres.
What the fuck?
Shallow elevation.
I like these names.
Existential pole star.
Prismatic DLC of blasphemy.
Let's call it the...
The robust...
Man.
No, can.
The robust can.
Keeping in style with the silly names, I guess.
Seed.
Randomize your world's seed.
Sure.
101.
Let's take that.
Size.
Ideal for a quick single-player experience.
Bigger and better for prolonged exploration.
Or bringing a friend.
And large.
Oh, I'm just noticing, by the way.
Terrarium.
In English, that means like a place for animals to hang out with glass around it, right?
And I'm just noticing the worlds have a little terrarium around it.
Almost like a fishbowl.
You see that?
That's a neat little detail.
Let's see.
What's this?
Super-sized for long-term progression and multiple players.
Um...
Let's just go with medium, I guess.
Okay, then we have...
What's this?
With great power...
Wait a minute, haven't I already chosen this?
With great power comes great responsibility.
Unearth your creativity.
Your adventure begins.
The standard Terraria experience.
Fortune and glory, kid.
Far greater difficulty and loot.
Master.
Game over, man.
Game over.
Brutally hard for the truly brave.
I mean, better loot?
Now I'm conflicted.
Uh...
What's this?
Let nature decide whether corruption or crimson infects your world.
Disease-like corruption is guaranteed to be present in your world.
Macabre grotesque crimson is guaranteed to be present in your world.
I don't know.
Honestly, I'm not sure about any of this.
This is random, fine.
But this is making me think I want to expert.
I mean, how hard can it be?
It's a fucking kids' game is what it looks like.
But then again, I said that about Minecraft 2.
And you know what?
I've beaten, uh, Rain World.
That's now on my curriculum vitae.
And I'm proud of it, bitch.
Um, maybe I'd even go Master.
Oh no, wait, this is...
Does that mean my character dies when I die?
Ooh, hold on.
I have beaten Rain World.
Should I go with Master?
I'm curious.
Maybe that's a bit too much.
Let's go expert.
Sure, whatever.
Here we go.
Generating jungle.
We need jungle, I'm afraid.
This desertification?
Setting liquids, nice.
The old man at the dungeon.
Uh, I didn't get to read it.
I don't know if I should read these.
You can assign or remove NPCs from houses.
From the housing interface.
Mouse 1.
Oh, fuck.
It's too fast!
Okay, so world has been made.
Sure.
Play.
Here we go.
Hey, Maxwell!
They say there is a person who will tell you how to survive on this land.
Oh wait, that's me.
Did you just puke a green slime?
Happiness.
I'm quite used to not having a home, but I wouldn't mind one.
Getting this place to myself, I greatly appreciate it.
I'm quite fond of wandering through the forest.
I like it here.
Weird.
This button named happiness.
Help.
You can...
Ah, wait.
Oh, that's gonna be annoying.
It's up here?
Oh, that's where that sound effect is from!
It's the sound effect I hear in every video.
Wait, what is...
Am I shooting a sword?
What's happening?
Oh my god.
Wait, I'm actually dying.
Hey.
Okay, I get it.
I get it.
Hey.
Don't...
Don't you...
Oh, I'm actually gonna die here.
How much HP do I have?
Oh, I got something.
I got gel.
How do I open inventory?
Oops.
Oh.
That's the map.
Oh, okay, so that's just like Minecraft.
Oh.
Oh, that's fitting.
Hold on.
An...
Annoying Copper Axe?
Hold on, I'm scared of that thing over there.
I'm gonna kill it.
Eh.
Yo, he's shooting something.
Oh, he's shooting a bow.
Right.
Ah!
No!
Fuck.
Oliver was decapitated by Blue Slime.
Well, there goes the no death stream.
I guess I wait.
You were slain.
Okay.
Oh, oh, that's cool.
Oliver was decapitated by Blue Slime March 31st, 2024.
Is that gonna stay there?
Edit?
Oliver was decap...
Oh, I can't write anything else.
I wanna go...
He fought...
bravely.
Nice.
Look at that.
That's awesome.
Man, I'm loving the atmosphere in this game.
It's very relaxing.
Hold on, what is my goal even?
I wonder if monsters come out at night.
Maxwell.
A bunny!
Greetings, Oliver.
Is there something I can help you with?
Um, help.
If you wanna survive, you will need to create weapons and shelter.
Start by chopping down trees and gathering wood.
Okay.
But wait, we got a dude over here.
Oh.
God, this is...
weirdly difficult.
Can I just...
I can't even hold it.
Oh, okay, okay.
Oh, look at that.
Teamwork.
Oh, I just dodged him so...
I thought it was not that sound effect when you get hit.
Hey.
Okay, chop down wood.
So I guess I need my annoying copper axe for that.
A red squirrel just came out.
Can I just hold it?
Nice.
Oh, timber.
Wood.
Wait, what did he say?
He said chop down a tree and...
Did he say build a house?
What's that, acorn?
Nice.
I got acorns.
Can I eat them?
Wait, what?
Oh!
Oh, I...
Okay.
That's it.
Uh, a Maxwell.
Uh, how do I build a house?
Um, hold on.
Maybe I should actually quickly...
Oh!
Copper...
Demonic copper pickaxe.
Why is it demonic?
I don't like that.
Five melee damage.
Very weak knockback.
Uh-oh, we've got slimes incoming.
Hey.
Hey, yo, slimes.
What's up, slime?
Oh, they have a lot of HP.
What the fuck?
Oh, I'm actually going to die here.
I just...
I just took some copper.
Yo, this is a big boy!
Ah!
Ugh!
You have not heard that sound.
Okay.
No!
Oh, I'm actually...
I'm half HP right now.
Oh, I can just spam it like this.
It's not gonna...
It can't even get close to me.
Oh, I jumped over there.
Oh, man.
Okay, this is more difficult than I thought.
Um...
So I press escape for inventory.
That's gotta be...
Is that really how I do that?
How about some other ERT?
Whoop!
Nope, don't do that.
Uh, Q.
C, V, B.
I want to go into the ma...
Does it pause?
It...
How do I menu?
Settings.
Okay, the game pauses.
Perfect.
Controls.
Let's see here.
Use item, interact.
Up, down, left, right.
Grapple.
Autos...
Smart cursor.
What?
Quick buff.
Throw.
How do I...
Is it really escape?
To go into the menu?
Or to into the...
It is!
Okay, wow.
Uh, maybe I want to put that on something else.
How about V?
That's better.
Escape is a little awkward for me.
Iron skin potion!
I'm gonna drink that.
I did it.
I have...
I now possess iron skin.
Dude, combat is weirdly difficult in this game.
Holy shit.
Hey, hey!
I wonder if it gets night.
Oh my god.
Ooh!
Why didn't that hit it?
That's so weird.
Eh.
Oh, I'm sorry Squirrel!
Oh no!
Come at me, bro.
Nice, I got money out of that.
I'm sorry, buddy.
Okay, so this is my bar.
This is my inventory.
Got it.
And then we have...
Money over here.
What's this?
Workbench.
Copper coin?
Crafting window.
Hold on, we've got enemies.
I just want to load a craft.
Oh, I see.
Needs 10 wood.
I have 42.
I can hit with the wood.
Hold on.
Workbench?
I clicked it now.
I'm so confused.
Let me get this money.
Maybe I need to...
Oh!
I just did something.
There.
How do I use it?
Oh, maybe it's automatically using, look.
I can make signs, fences.
A fishing pole!
Yes!
I want that.
Put it there.
A bow!
Yes, dude!
Oh, we can even make it immediately.
This is easy.
Let's put that on.
You know what, actually?
Hold on.
I think it's getting night.
I'm going to do something.
Settings.
I need to mirror Minecraft here for my hotbar.
So, let's see.
Put this back on escape, I guess.
Let's see...
Where's 1, 2, 3, 4...
This?
What?
What is D1?
Oh, okay.
7 becomes C.
8 becomes V.
And 9, R.
Hopefully, I didn't overwrite something just now.
And 10 is...
I don't...
B.
Let's see if I overwrote something.
Okay, R is already...
Let's put that on something else, like...
I don't know, why?
Why not, right?
That's J, I believe.
B, quickbuff.
Let's put that on...
Zed?
Journey powers?
I don't know what that is.
That's probably for the journey style.
Hold on.
How about K for that?
Sure.
Why not?
Oh, that's annoying, why doesn't it show my key mines up here?
That's gonna mess me up later.
CV.
Okay.
Now I have a bow, but I don't have any arrows.
I think that's what that number means.
Alright, let me fuck this guy up.
I should probably make a house before the night hits.
Kill him!
Max, we'll get him!
Come on.
Yeah, you got him, you got him.
Yes! One more.
Shoot him!
Yes, dude!
Thanks!
Oh, you wanted to say something.
I'm here to give you advice on what to do next.
It is recommended that you talk with me anytime you get stuck.
Thank you.
Okay, let me go to my crafting bench.
And pull up this.
And...
Let me see here.
Yeah, so it's proximity.
How do I make a house with a hammer?
Let me actually chop some more wood.
I think I used most of my wood.
Oh, no, wait, I have 13 wood, but maybe I need more.
I'm gonna make a sweet house.
Chop it!
Nice.
Got more acorns.
Another slime!
Maxwell!
Can I hit him with this?
Oh, that's pretty good.
Oh, you can totally stagger them.
Oh, this is easy.
Not even a problem at all.
Okay, no, this one.
Also, I need to change these.
No, no, no.
Okay, I see.
Oh, no, it's getting dark.
Okay, let's try and build a house.
It's house time.
I can make breastplate and shit.
Oh, ah, here we go.
The slimes, though! Woodwall!
Make a woodwall!
Oh my god, this is so confusing.
Iron skin.
God damn it.
Maybe I should not have picked the difficulty that was difficult.
Okay, it's getting really dark.
Zombie!
This ain't good, this ain't good, this ain't good.
I need to make...
Where's my wall? There.
How does this work?
Wait, I need more.
Make a munch.
No!
No, I made work benches!
Fuck!
Oh no.
Hold on, I need to chop some more wood.
Fuck me!
Come on!
Are you okay, Maxwell? You need assistance.
Yo, this works pretty well.
Even though they have a lot of HP, holy crap.
Come here.
Maxwell does a shit ton of damage.
He's not jokin' around a torch.
Can I put that?
Put it on a tree.
Hey! Look at that!
Yes!
Maybe that will prevent monsters from coming.
Okay.
Put that there.
Weird how it automatically sort of sorts the inventory for you.
Okay, now that we have some working lights, let's think about this.
Uh...
I need to make...
crafting window.
And then a shit ton of...
wall.
Let's do that.
What the fuck is that?
Oh!
Maxwell!
Oh, get into the light, into the light.
Be gone, foul demon!
It's not even aiming for me, it's like, it's weird.
What's Maxwell?
Maxwell.
Maxwell!
Help me!
We've got enemies!
We've got demon eyes!
Oh, shit.
Okay, we gotta get back to the light.
Take torch, put torches, every...
layer.
Uh, switch? No, no, no.
Get out of here and switch to that, and then...
Maxwell is not helping at all here.
I'm fighting for my life, dude.
Can I sprint?
Wait, I just did something.
Oh!
I have a torch in my hand.
Well, that's kinda useful, actually.
Oh no, we've got multiple enemies inbound.
Dude, I need to make better weapons!
This is shit!
The music is oddly relaxing.
Come on, come on, come on.
Oh my god, we've got zombies!
No!
Oh!
All he was put on the wrong side of the grass by demon eye.
Holy shit.
Cheers.
Okay, so it's definitely confirmed.
Monsters come out at night, and Maxwell is not helping at all.
So he's losing HP here.
I'm kinda worried.
Let's build a massive wall.
Oh, you can...
You can build it up like that as well.
How do I keep them out, though?
I'm gonna wall myself in.
It's not working.
I need to make some kind of pillar, I think.
Oh my god.
Just kill them, kill them.
I'm protecting you!
Oh my god, they do a lot of damage.
Don't jump on me.
Oh no!
Maxwell!
Come on, you got this.
You got this, buddy.
Do I have to wait?
Okay.
Maxwell!
No, he's leaving!
I gotta rescue him.
Okay, okay, let's go.
Holy shit.
Oh, okay, nice.
They're following me now, so that gives him an opportunity to hit him.
Okay, okay.
Oh yeah, the damage on all of them.
So after they jump, I have a small window.
What the fuck is that?
I'm gonna take that.
Fallen star.
Thanks.
No.
Dude, I'm terrible.
This game is difficult.
Okay, okay.
I need to...
you know, reorganize my expectations here.
Why do these cute games always end up being so difficult?
That's my question.
Okay, quickly.
Craft.
What can I...
Bench.
Make me craft a...
I don't even know.
Sand...
I don't know.
I need some kind of different way of putting down the wall that will not allow these monsters to get in.
Oh, no.
I'm already low HP.
Max will get back here.
There's a flying eye now as well.
Okay, I'm gonna jump over these guys.
Can I at least look at my while I wait?
I want to look at the crafting while I'm dead.
I have 100 HP.
I have day bloom seeds and a bow that I can't use yet.
Okay, quickly.
I craft.
Crafting.
Oh, wait.
What did I just do?
What is that?
All that was chopped up by zombie.
Bro, this...
I need this to be day.
This night is fucking me up.
We need daytime.
I don't do well at night.
Is that guy throwing things at me?
I need some food as well so I can heal.
Or health potion or something.
I like the music though.
The music is very nice.
Oh, I'm gonna die again here.
We've got more coming in from the left.
It's unreal.
Oh, I was trying to jump over him, but then he jumped in the air.
That's terrible.
My goodness.
Okay, okay.
Maxwell the guide was slain.
Oh, fuck.
This is bad.
I kind of need...
I need him.
For multiple reasons.
Okay, you know what?
New strategy.
Yeah.
We're just gonna die here real quick.
This is part of the strategy.
And then we're gonna figure out how the fuck we built a wall.
Wood wall.
I'm definitely doing something there though.
Like, how am I getting past these guys?
Maybe when they jump, I run.
Yeah, there we go.
Ah, they jump while I... when I jump.
You can't get past them.
I feel like I fucked up.
Ooh, what's happening now?
Uh-oh.
There's mists.
Wait, quiet neighborhood.
Oh man.
What is the quiet neighborhood?
Enter a misty graveyard filled with the surely dead.
Okay.
Bro, I'm gonna set a record here for
dying the most times in the early game, I think.
This is horrible.
Wow.
Okay, can I at least craft a better weapon?
Come on, let's think.
Monsters are gone, monsters are gone.
Let's see, what can I make?
Let me try and make a hammer.
What can I do with that?
Can I do something here?
Oh, I can destroy the wall, that's not what I want though.
Okay, we gotta run.
Fallen star, can I eat those?
You can do it, thanks.
I believe the game is believing in me.
I can do it, damn it.
I believe it.
How do I eat this?
Ooh, I just did something.
Maybe I can warp them off like that, hold on.
Oh my god.
Be gone, I have the star!
No, okay.
Jump.
You bastard!
They're not jumping when I want them to jump.
Man, hopefully Maxwell is going to respawn here, or I'm going to be fucked.
I feel like I'm not going to be surviving very long.
Campfire, yes!
Let's do it.
Why can't I make one?
Ah, there we go.
Oh, that's nice.
That's actually really nice.
Wood platform?
Sure, let's do it.
Also, let's kill this guy first.
Okay.
A new dawn.
A new chance to redeem myself.
Come on, take damage on the fire at least.
Oh god, I'm terrible at this.
Oh my god.
Holy shit!
Why is this so difficult?
What's happening now?
Oh no, I'm entering the graveyard thingy.
Okay, he's taking care of it at least.
Jump.
Just one of you jump!
Aw, man.
Okay, don't be in the graveyard.
I decided to build my house there it seems, which is a bad idea.
Hold on, I just want to quickly see here in the controls if there's anything I'm missing regarding the building here.
Interact.
Smart.
Quick heal.
I should try that.
Zoom out.
Demi plus.
Wait.
Loadout.
Map controls.
Yeah, I'm not quite sure.
Okay, come on.
We got this.
First of all, let's get out of this place.
We're probably going to die again because there's two zombies right there.
Yep, there we go.
That's how you do it.
You got to be at range so they jump towards you.
Maybe they are warded off by the sunlight.
Oh, I have an idea. I have an idea.
Can we...
Oh, of course I can dig.
I'm an idiot.
I have an idea.
We're digging down.
This is very awkward.
Actually, it's fine.
Dig.
Move the grass.
Okay.
Question.
Can I put these blocks back?
Third block.
There it is.
I have finally become safe.
Yes, dude.
It's happening.
Okay.
Now I want torches.
Wait.
Are there cucumbers?
No, okay.
There.
Ooh, yeah.
Of course you can dig.
What am I thinking?
Okay, I'm getting some stuff here.
Maybe this will unlock some new items for me so I can actually build a house.
Oh, wait.
I should not jump down because what if I can't get up again?
Also, let me...
Ugh.
Fucking get away from me.
Okay.
First things first.
I have enough crafting benches.
Workbench.
Let's put one here.
And now...
Let's see.
Oh, yeah.
Look, we unlocked new things.
I can...
Oh, I can scroll here.
Wood greaves.
You know what?
Let's make some goddamn wood stuff.
Greaves.
Is that a...
Are those for the hands of the boots?
I actually don't know.
Equitable.
Emotes window.
Beastiary.
Nice.
Let's see here.
Ah, here.
Okay.
Perfect.
Nice.
So those are boots.
Oh, wait.
What's this?
Housing.
Social accessory?
Camera mode.
Equipment.
Ah, loadouts.
Huh.
Cool.
Um, nice.
Nice, nice.
What else can I make?
Not much.
Okay, so it will only show you things you can craft if you have the materials for it.
It won't even show them grayed out.
If you don't have the materials,
you can't do shit.
That's what I'm getting from this.
So let's see here.
I'm going to take some more stone.
I want to make stone tools.
It's finally happening.
We're terraering.
That's even a word.
Block this up again.
I wonder though, let me quickly test something.
Does the water flow in here?
Do that?
Is that simulated?
Oh, nice.
Oh, that's cool.
That's pretty neat.
I like it.
Okay.
I have all kinds of things here.
Peace theory.
Ah, nighttime.
Guide.
The guide always offers useful advice and crafting recipes.
His origins and unusual connections to this world remain a mystery.
I see.
Why is there a star on him?
Can I rate him 5 out of 5 stars?
Okay.
Emotes.
I don't want that.
Sword inventory?
Yes!
An auto sword!
Now that's what I'm talking about.
I like that.
Stone wall.
Mud block.
I think I just realized how to build a house.
It just occurred to me.
I just do what I did here.
But with blocks.
I get it.
Hold on.
Let's just wait for these slimes to pass.
And then we're going to get up.
And then we're going to build a house.
What is this?
20 out of 20.
What's this?
Oh.
Wait, how did I just...
Sure, this is fine.
Okay, let's go.
Oh.
There we go.
Okay.
Quick.
Let's see here.
B. No, not B.
Escape.
I'm going to use stone blocks.
There.
Wall.
Nice.
R.
Quick, quick, quick.
Quick!
Look at that.
Look at that!
Hey, hey, hey.
Hey.
You can't get to me now.
Can I get to them, though, through the wall?
Can I cheese them?
Okay, I can't test it now.
So what about this wall?
What is the point?
Is this just aesthetics?
Okay, I ran out of wall.
Cozy fire.
Life regen is slightly increased.
Oh, cool.
So that's a buff that lasts for a while, I guess.
Because I'm not that close to the campfire.
What else do I have in my inventory right now?
Do I have more wood?
I have dirt blocks.
Okay, let me cheese you guys.
No, it doesn't work!
That's a bummer.
Okay, I do need to get some wood here.
Let me venture outside.
Wait, I could make a door, right?
Come on.
Give me that tree.
What about the stump?
Can I get the stump?
Maybe not.
More tree.
Come on, come on, come on.
Yes!
Ooh, that's satisfying.
Give me that too.
Yes!
Okay, let me take care of you.
You ain't shit, boy.
You ain't shit!
Okay, you're quite a lot, actually.
Okay, oh, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Nice.
Okay, now we're going to put down another bench.
Because I have enough.
Let's see...
No, V.
There.
You can't get in, bitch.
There's a little worm in my hut.
Look.
Goddamn.
Craft.
Wood wall, I guess.
Just make a bunch.
And put it here.
Whoops.
That looks nice.
Wait, what's the...
Oh, shit.
Okay, fine.
All right, fine.
Man, there's many slimes.
I just want to sit here and take a swig while I look at these guys.
Okay.
What else can I make?
I can make...
Wooden breastplate, I should do that.
Nice.
I need the fence.
I need a lot of that.
Wood helmet.
Yes, sir.
Oh.
Matching attire.
Heck yeah.
And then we're also gonna make...
What's this? Accessories.
Okay.
Wait, there's no gloves.
Gotcha.
Look at me!
I have a wooden armor.
That's so silly.
When you think about it, it's so weird.
Okay, I can destroy things from the inside.
How do I remove this?
Was that the hammer?
Ah, okay.
I want to make...
No, no, no, no, no!
Why can't I place it?
Oh no.
Ooh.
Is this an STP?
Wait.
Ooh, wait, did I take damage?
It's coming in here.
Stone block.
Why can't I...
I see, I see, I see.
Okay.
Are you gonna come in here?
Oh, look at that.
It's an STP.
Like that.
I want to make it look nice.
Oh no, oh no.
No, no, no!
Get out of my house!
There we go.
Wait, the goddamn...
Oh.
How do I just get that circle?
Or like the yellow square to come up?
There we go!
That looks nice.
And then...
Let's put a torch as well.
Nice.
Okay.
What's next?
Make chairs.
Dirt wall.
Oh, I could have just made a dirt hut, of course.
Arrows!
Yeah, dude.
Stone blocks and any wood.
It makes sense.
Oh, and arrows.
You can have a lot of them, it seems.
It just works?
Hold on.
Put this in my...
Actually put it...
There.
Ho-ho-ho-ho-ho-ho-ho!
Here we go.
Also, what's this?
Heel.
Okay, I'm full health.
I need to make a door.
Wait, can I shoot them through this?
Jump.
Yeah!
Okay, this totally works.
I can farm them like this.
Look!
Oh my god, it does so much damage too!
Holy shit!
Oh!
I love it!
Okay, this guy has a lot of HP still.
Oh yeah, you're getting farmed now, bitch.
Look at that fucking shot!
Sniper in the house.
How do I make these guys not spawn?
Get away from me.
Oh, it's getting night again.
That's fine, we have a hut this time.
Everything is fine.
Look at that!
Okay, let's make a door.
Door, door, door.
I think we need some more wood.
Let me quickly gather it before nightfall.
Hurry, hurry, hurry!
Thanks.
See ya.
And then...
I guess you run out of arrows quick.
Nice.
Okay, quick.
Door?
Wooden door.
Oh, look at that!
Awesome!
Okay, things are going well.
What else should I make?
I can make a table, a sign.
You know what?
Maybe I should craft one of...
Ooh, jester's arrow.
This is five range of damage.
Flaming arrow.
Yo!
What does this require, though?
Oh, torch.
It totally makes sense.
Oh, no, I didn't mean to.
Okay, fine.
I guess we have some flaming arrows now.
Oh, wait, I think I understand.
Ah, that's how you do it.
Okay, gotcha.
I guess the prioritization must come from the top.
So if I were to shoot now...
Yep, works.
That was actually kind of risky.
What if my shit caught on fire?
I just realized.
I don't know why I just did that.
That makes no sense.
Uh, let's see here.
I'm gonna make one of each.
Because maybe that will unlock more things.
I can just put a table on the wall.
Oh, no, he's trying to get in!
Uh...
Can he get in?
Can I see the health of this door?
Uh-oh.
Uh...
I'm assuming he can't get in.
Everything's fine.
Put a table.
Man, I need to expand my house here.
I don't have any room at all.
Hotbar unlocked.
Cool.
You can plan out your buildings.
Here's what I can do, though.
I can build like this.
I don't have to go outside.
Let's make a...
Oh, I have to be within the range, though.
We're gonna have a second room here?
Actually, we're just gonna expand a little bit.
What's the difference?
Oh, it's just easier to see what you're hitting.
I see.
Okay, and then we need wall.
That's not wall.
This is wall.
Oh, I don't have enough.
Shit!
Uh...
I need more wall.
Make like 20.
That's a good amount.
Oh, it's like automatically, uh...
sort of doing it.
Then we need this.
To remove...
I don't know, how do I...
I don't understand.
That's okay.
Why can't I put this here, though?
Ah, there we go.
Okay, fine.
Uh...
There we go.
I can sort of put dirt back,
but I can also remove dirt.
It's a little bit weird how this works.
Look.
I don't know what determines one or the other here.
Okay, I'm just waiting for night, uh,
for dawn right now, actually.
What else should I make?
Let's see.
I can make...
jester's arrow.
It's just...
weak knockback.
Okay.
Copper coins.
And wood can be placed.
Oh, wait a minute.
Is this like, uh...
Oh, I get it now.
This is the equivalent of the stone.
Okay.
Also, this zombie right here is, uh,
scaring me a little bit.
Let's make another door.
Uh, I can't.
I don't have enough wood.
You know what?
I kind of want to kill this guy.
Real bad.
Yeah, I've died a lot over here.
This is, uh, terrible.
I'm gonna farm these fools right now.
I'm gonna open a little hole.
Oh, yeah.
Look, they take damage over time.
Isn't that glorious?
Yep.
Oh, it's coming inside.
That's not good.
Die. Die. Die.
Nice.
Is this going pretty well?
Why is there a...
Can I remove that?
Hammer?
Ah, there we go.
How do I put this back?
No.
There we go.
Oh, we've got a thingy.
Uh-oh.
We've got two zombies now.
Come on, Dawn.
How many arrows do I have left?
Fourteen.
That's not enough.
I need to make more.
Let's make these.
That requires Fallen Star.
Okay.
Hell yeah.
Oh, here he comes.
What is that in his hand?
Is that a shotgun?
No, that's a torch.
Come on.
Can I make anything else while I wait here?
I can make a fence!
That's probably going to keep them out.
Also, I can make more.
You know, I should do that.
I should do that.
Make a bunch of arrows.
Dude, I need way more wood.
Like, I need to be chopping a shit-ton of wood here.
This is not enough wood.
Not even close.
Also, I want to use the fishing pole,
but not when there's enemies.
Lemon!
Minor improvements to all stats.
When life gives you lemons.
Nice.
I should eat it.
Look, well fed.
I now have minor improvements to all stats
and increased life regeneration.
I feel confident that I can head out
and kick some ass.
Oh, it's lighting up too.
That's so cool.
Yo, this is going through them.
Penetrate of power.
That's awesome.
I wonder if there's a way to quickly switch
between the different arrow types I have.
Okay, things are coming together here, dude.
I can even chop wood during the night.
I'm not afraid.
Easy.
Yeah.
I need to make a better pickaxe.
Or axe, I should say.
Okay, what is that?
A zombie.
Begone?
Oh, that doesn't do a lot of damage, actually.
I need to...
Okay, nice.
We got some wood.
Let's make...
What can I make here?
A sign.
I guess I can make a chair.
Dirt wall.
Sign.
How do I unlock more things to make?
Used for basic crafting.
Okay.
Okay, nice. Dawn is coming.
It's finally time to get some work done.
When dawn comes, I'm going to chop a shit ton of wood.
And we're going to go mining.
Because when we're underground, we'll be safe.
Also, I should make some more...
No, I have enough torches.
Let's put torches on five.
And I can probably...
Use the mushrooms to make some stew or something.
Oh.
There comes another star.
Guys, can you please leave me alone?
I hate that they're standing here just knocking on my door.
Guys, come on.
Can I make a window?
I probably need glass, so I need sand for that.
Maybe this is easier to scroll like this.
Maybe there's a different sub-menu here or something.
I want to make one of each in case it unlocks something.
Let's make a dirt wall.
Let's make another door, actually.
I'm going to put it here.
There. Nice. Look at that.
Oh, it automatically opens.
Oh, that's actually so nice.
I love that.
That's a great feature.
Okay, thon is coming.
Shot all this. Nice.
Get away from me.
God, I love the bow.
The bow is so much better than the sword. Holy shit.
The sword sucks.
Oh, I have no more arrows.
Oh, no. Oh, no.
I'm forced to use the sword.
Why did I go this way?
Come on.
Wait for them to jump.
Come on, jump.
And I'll go. Yeah!
There we go.
Yes!
Juiced, bitch!
You ain't got shit on me.
Okay, nice.
Oh, I got iron ore.
Can be placed.
Sure.
I can make an iron home.
Shiny.
Does that mean I can build more things?
All of his body was mangled by zombie.
Okay, it's done.
It's time to just collect a bunch of shit.
I'm gonna just collect a bunch of wood first.
Get this as well.
Also, it looks like there's infinite durability on these, by the way.
Like, this axe has been going forever.
It's an annoying copper axe.
Also copper axe, that sounds horrible.
Copper is a very soft metal.
Come on, get it. Get it. Get it.
Oh, you fucking bastard.
Oh, no. I'm actually gonna die.
Oh, no, don't go that way. Don't go that way.
It's a terrible idea.
I need to make arrows, like, right now.
Okay, that's fine. That's fine.
That's fine. That's fine.
Oh, it has something in it. Look.
There's a little thing embedded in the center of this slime.
Okay, get inside.
Arrows.
Make a shit ton of arrows.
Yeah, just make it.
No hobo.
Oh, man.
I'll make flaming arrows.
No, jester's arrows.
Why? Because I can.
Like that.
And now...
Hey!
Wait, Joe.
I thought you were Maxwell. Never mind.
Um...
I got a bone out too, look!
Oh my god.
Get him. Who the fuck is Joe?
Have you come to visit my humble establishment?
I'm here to give you advice on what to do next.
It is recommended that you talk with me any time you get stuck.
Where's Maxwell?
And what have you done with him?
Help.
Underground are crystal hearts,
which can be used to increase your max life.
You can smash them with a pickaxe.
Nice.
Tell me about crafting, please.
Wait, what?
Huh?
Wait.
Obtain an anvil made from iron or lead.
Oh!
You want an anvil? Wait.
Wait, three defense?
Oh, never mind. I thought it was on the ground over here.
I was so confused.
I guess it's from these. One defense, one defense, one defense.
Perfect.
Joe!
Crafting.
Can I emote to you?
He's waking at me.
He's like sword. You want to fight?
Happiness.
Getting this place to myself, I greatly appreciate it.
I'm quite fond of wandering through the forest.
I like it here.
Sure. Happiness.
I don't get it. Crafting.
I don't get this. What do you mean crafting?
Yes, I know I can craft.
Tell me how to craft more.
Help.
If you gather five fallen stars, they can be combined
to create an item that will increase your magic capacity.
Wait, what does that mean?
Am I a mage?
God, I love how they look at those arrows.
They're neat.
Okay, I'm wasting time.
It's time to chop down some shit.
Balloon!
Just part of the background.
Speaking of the background, very nice.
We're right by a lake here.
Nice view in the distance.
Oh, don't go that way.
It's a nice scary graveyard.
Okay, we're going to go down.
Actually, I have a better idea.
Joe, this is my house.
Greetings, Oliver. Is there something I can help you with?
Help.
Stars fall all over the world at night.
They can be used for all sorts of useful things.
If you see one, be sure to grab it
because they disappear after sunrise.
Damn it.
Okay, thanks.
Thanks, Joe!
You're the man. I don't know what happened to Maxwell,
but I'll take it.
I'm going to make a tunnel from here.
And let's not make it straight down
because then we can't get up again.
Let's be smart about this.
What's that?
Clay block!
What is that?
It's just stone.
Okay.
I'm going to make a sort of diagonal
dig here.
And I'm super safe because
I can go straight into my house. I hope I can make a ladder or something.
So I need some light here.
Oh, look!
You can see further! Just holding it!
That's cool as hell.
Uh...
I like this music.
Yes! This is just like Minecraft.
This is awesome.
Well, the whole placing tortures while you go into mines, right?
Also, I can't help but
feel like I need a shovel for this dirt.
Also, what is this again?
Hold on. I want something in the...
I need to see something real quick.
Smart cursor.
Oh, it just automatically selects
anything close to my cursor.
Oh, that's actually...
That's actually not too bad.
I mean, it's a little less manual.
I mean, you don't have as much precision, but...
I guess if you're just
looking to dig some shit.
See, I didn't want to mind that,
but he did it anyway.
Yeah, okay, this is a bit weird.
Hold on, let me go back to this.
Okay.
Joe! How you doing up there?
Can I talk to you from here?
No. Oh, I can even see his HP like this.
In fact, I can see everyone's HP.
I wonder if I can give Joe
some better weapons here.
We can defend himself properly.
You know what?
I wonder if I can give myself better weapons first.
How about we start with that, huh?
This music is so cute.
Oh, what's that?
Tin.
I'm gonna take that!
Also, is that a...
There's a cave here!
Oh, look at the tin, it's...
slightly glowing.
I'm taking it.
It is mine.
Dude, I'm so...
I think I'm gonna be
living in the mines.
The surface is some bullshit, man.
So many enemies there.
I feel much safer down here.
I'm just chilling.
Okay.
We've got stalagmites or stalactites.
I never am able to remember which is which.
How do I get back up, though, is the question here?
Hold on, there was actually something.
I remember now.
Controls. Grapple.
Let's see how that works.
I'm pressing it.
Oh, no.
Oh, cobweb!
Oh, no, that means they're spiders.
I don't like that. I hate that, in fact.
Okay, this is fine. How can I get...
Oh, I can kind of jump far here.
It's not... Oh, I'm hearing something.
Let's get rid of this piece right here.
Oh, I'm an idiot.
I can just do this!
Why am I overthinking this? Holy shit.
Of course I can do that. I can ascend, probably.
Ascension.
I know all about ascension.
That's nice.
Look at the parallax there on the background.
That's cool.
Ooh!
I can't place torches here.
Wait, why can't I even...
Shurikens!
No way.
Shuriken.
Ten range of damage.
Very fast speed. No knockback.
Consumable?
Fuck you, mean.
Oh, like, usable.
I was like, can you eat those?
I don't want to eat them.
What are you talking about, dude?
Hey, there's loot down here.
Okay, there's also a guy down there. I gotta be careful there.
Can I not just... Ah, nice.
Oh, there's a door. I didn't even see that.
Let's wait for this guy to turn around. There we go.
Oh, the cobwebs!
Uh...
Get him!
Oh, look at this!
It's like a little house!
Get rid of all the cobwebs.
Dude, I'm liking how this looks.
What's that?
Is that an anvil?
Hold on, can I craft things on this?
Wait, webrope.
Oh, probably because I got some spiderwebs.
Let's make a bunch of this.
Let me see.
Oh, my God!
Oh, that's so useful!
I like it.
Give me all the cobwebs.
Oh, the cobwebs actually gets destroyed.
Quick, here.
Chest.
I am loot.
Demonic maze!
Dude, that's just crazy.
Upgrade.
20 damage.
Can be upgraded with torches.
Angel statue.
And normal ass rope.
Sure.
Tungsten bar! Damn!
More shuriken.
Can I shift click this?
I can, okay. Silver coins.
Angel statue can be placed.
Dude, I'm gonna get on with this right here.
Oh, my God!
Look at that!
Can I take this with me? I kinda want this back home.
Hey!
Awesome!
Can I take this with me?
Wait, does an anvil statue?
Wait, what?
Wait, wait.
What?
This is a huge troll.
It's a statue of an anvil.
That's so stupid!
Okay.
I've got a little board there with a heart on it.
Dude, I kinda wanna make this my base now.
This is way better looking than what I have.
What's this?
Reaper statue.
Yeah, I don't like that.
Okay, that's so weird though.
Okay, you know what?
I've gotten some stuff.
It's time to...
webrope.
No.
Oh, yeah!
Look at that!
Hey!
Awesome.
But here I can actually just jump.
But I do wanna remove this.
In fact, hold on.
Just take that.
Remove this.
Look at that.
Easy access when we go back up.
Oh, this is annoying.
Get that out of there.
Cool!
And here I can even make one of these two.
Wow, I actually ran out of that.
That was fast.
But I can make more.
You know what? I'm gonna save my cobweb.
In case I can use it for other things.
Joe! Check it out!
I brought a bunch of stuff to the chest.
I'm gonna put that.
Oh shit, I don't have room.
Also, this chair should maybe be next to the
table.
That would make sense.
Okay, leave this here for now.
I'm gonna put the Reaper statue out here.
Maybe they will scare off predators.
The Reaper is here.
Don't enter.
Um...
Okay, I should be able to craft more things now.
Yes, look at this.
A furnace!
Now we're goddamn talking.
Okay.
I gotta expand my house, though.
This is...
I don't need a small house like that.
I am a man of culture.
And I deserve a house that is big and great.
I need more stone.
Do I, though?
I don't think I do.
Everything is fine. Oh!
He damaged me through the wall!
You bastard!
Oh my god.
Get rid of the statue!
Uh, six...
Gabra!
There it is. I'm safe. Everything is fine.
And now? Dirt.
Just fill this up with dirt.
That.
What? Oh, no, no, no.
Okay, there we go. Perfect!
Also, I'm just thinking.
We should probably make some flooring, too.
Joe, you went in the hole!
That's okay.
Okay.
Do I have any walls?
I have a little bit.
Okay, that's all I have.
Let's put a torch.
It's a little bit odd the way the torches placement work.
It's like, sometimes it doesn't register.
It's a little bit weird.
Okay, here we go.
I'm gonna go try to fight these guys.
I'm gonna go fight slimes.
Oh my god!
What?
Yo, this is sick!
Wait, why is this not extending?
Oh, I see!
You're charging it.
Yo, this is amazing.
Yo, the game is easy.
Now we put dirt.
Oh, we got a star as well.
I don't need...
Friendship ended with bow.
The demonic maze is now my best friend.
In fact, I'm gonna venture into
the graveyard here.
I have the demonic maze.
I fear nothing.
Look at that damage!
Looks like it damages it
on the way there and when it returns.
That's nice.
Also, why is there a...
Graveyard? Oh, wait, I think I understand.
There's a graveyard here because I died so many times.
It's a graveyard.
I get it.
That's why it's a goddamn graveyard.
Wow.
This is getting a little scary.
Oh!
Okay, okay, okay.
It's even better than I thought.
Holy shit, that's OP as fuck.
I love it.
Look at that!
Yo, what do you mean, slow?
Oh, look at this.
It says very slow speed
and I have no idea what you're talking about.
Place, there we go.
Okay, here we go.
I can't believe I finally figured out
where that sound effect is coming from
that everybody uses in their videos.
It's from Terraria!
You.
That's a goddamn ghost.
Nice.
Also, I should be careful here.
What's that?
A zombie.
Okay.
Do I get experience?
Can I level myself up or somehow?
I mean, I guess I did level myself up
by having this maze.
You know what I mean?
I should go chop down some wood.
I fear nothing right now.
In fact, I should eat.
I can eat a mushroom.
I should have something on the ready.
Let's see here.
Put that there, I guess.
Also, the shuriken.
10 range of damage.
Put this here instead.
This is like my Minecraft keybinds.
What was that?
Yellow marigold.
Ah, we got another star.
Hey, bitch!
Bro, this is insane.
This demonic maze kicks ass.
And it said something can be upgraded with torches.
How does that work?
Rope?
Okay, I can make new things as well.
Squirrel!
See you, squirrel.
Let's chop some wood.
Heck yeah.
So, I'm gonna expand my house.
I'm gonna make a furnace.
And then hopefully I can smell some shit
and make better axes.
That's my current goal in the game.
In case you were wondering.
You...
Bro, this is crazy.
Like this weapon right here just
fucking upped my game by a million.
Can I remove these graves?
I don't want there to be a graveyard.
Here's like a bad idea.
I wonder if some of these
zombies that I'm fighting are me
awakened from the dead.
Oh, you.
Hey!
God, I love the way this arrow looks.
Look at the sniper. Oh, sick!
Okay, the combat is satisfying.
I'm liking the combat.
In the beginning I was a little bit...
I don't know, it seems a little old, you know.
But this is great!
Dude, I'm fucking killing everything.
Look at this guy, it's nothing.
Put down some torches as well.
Just light up this entire place.
Make it look nice and cozy.
I need to eat.
Do I then wait? I see.
Okay, okay. Wait, potion sickness.
What's up with that?
Hey, you!
Okay, they just keep coming, I guess.
I mean...
They do drop a bunch of silver.
Hopefully I can trade that with someone
to get some nice stuff.
I love the way my character looks
when he jumps like, hey!
Thank you.
Actually, they drop items all the time.
I should really see what they...
Oh, thank you.
Oh, this is so satisfying.
I got to say though, the bow is still kind of cool.
But this weapon right here
is awesome as well. And there's no durability, it seems.
So...
This is mine to keep.
For the foreseeable future, I guess.
Okay, we've got some wood now.
270.
That's nice.
Let's use that wood to craft things.
And let's also take a look
at what else we can do.
A wooden yo-yo.
Let's make a bunch of wall.
Let's say...
100.
There.
And then...
Let's also have some...
rope coil.
Throw to create a climbable line of rope.
Oh!
Yo, wait a minute. Does that work the way I think it does?
Hold on a sec.
Let's say I'm down here, right?
Wait...
Wait, what?
I don't get it.
Where's...
rope coil?
Oh, it became...
Oh, I get it.
I see now.
So we have rope in our inventory.
I can coil it up
and get ready for a throw, right?
Maybe to reach high up places.
And that's all that is.
Plus three range right now.
But if I make a rope coil...
I was expecting it to say more range there.
But that's okay.
So if I'm down here, let's say
and I go like this.
Oh, cool.
I see now.
And then I can actually use this now
to extend it.
Yes.
That's cool.
Get rid of this shit.
I hate that I hit my head every time I try to get up here.
Joe, are you stuck down here?
Do you want me to...
you know...
Hopefully there's no friendly fire here.
Joe, I'm gonna let you in on a secret here.
I have no idea what I'm doing.
And I need your help.
So can you please get up here?
Just get rid of all this for now.
I can place it later.
Get rid of this wall right here.
And then...
Just fill all of this up with some
nice wall in the back. Looks nice.
And there we go. Look at that.
Beautiful stuff.
Okay.
Get rid of this because it's ugly.
Beautiful.
Now, I need to...
I wonder if I can make a trap door here
instead of having to just, you know,
do it like that.
But wait, I did actually see something.
Workbench.
Put the workbench
here for now.
Get next to it.
And then we're gonna craft...
I did see a platform, didn't I?
Platform.
Is that what I think it is?
Hold on.
Hey, he's happy about that.
Oh, he wants fish.
Joe, say no more, fam.
I'm gonna bring you a fish.
Look at this.
Yes, we've got floors, baby.
Yo, this is great.
Oh, I have to remove this.
Oh, wait. I ran out. Okay.
I see.
Make more.
Make like a shit ton of these.
Yes.
Yes, man.
That's beautiful.
Okay.
And then I need to make a hole here
and make trap doors of some sort.
But first, put this back here.
And then...
What else can I make?
I can make a mana crystal.
Permanently increases mana by 20.
Oh, that's what that is.
Oh, I've got mana.
Okay.
I can make a tiki torch.
I don't know what that is.
But I'm gonna make a furnace now.
Put it there.
Yeah.
I can make bars.
Oh, shit.
Joe!
Protect me.
I need to make doors.
Joe, move your ass.
Get out of here.
Joe!
He's protecting me.
That's fine.
Let's make some...
iron bars.
Nice.
Oh, I can make new things now!
I can make plates.
I can make red bricks.
Tin brick. Iron brick.
Let's make some tin bars.
Clay pot.
Also, let me actually just put this back.
Let's put it next to the chair.
Isn't that chair a little small?
I feel like that's a small chair.
Can I sit in the chair?
Hey, look at this.
I should have another chair for me and Joe.
Chair.
Make a chair.
I need to go over here.
Look at that!
That's beautiful.
Let's take this torch
and put it on the table.
Look at that!
That's amazing.
Amazing.
Door goes back.
Wait.
Why doesn't that work?
Oh, no.
Wait.
Hold on.
Is this not flooring?
Maybe I just need to make wood.
Let me do this instead.
Hold on. We're going to change up a little bit here.
Let me try something new.
Oh, you know what? This actually looks way better, too.
Yeah.
Let's go like that.
Actually, let's quickly test here.
Before this thing comes.
Wait, it still doesn't work.
What has to work?
Slime.
Hey, there it is.
Okay.
So, you do need a special type of floor here.
I get it.
Good thing these things don't fall down when I remove the floor.
Oh, no.
I need one more.
Just make a lot of it, actually.
In fact, we need a lot of wood.
Look at that.
Things are coming together here.
This is starting to look like a proper home.
How do I remove this little
leftover wall there?
It's kind of annoying me.
Mmm.
Joe.
Help me.
There are many different ways you can attract people
to move into our town.
They will, of course, need a home to live in.
You don't say.
In order for a room to be
considered a home,
it needs to have a door, a chair,
a table, and a light source.
Make sure the house
has walls as well. Well,
good.
I have all that.
Help.
Two people will not live in the same home.
Also, if their home is destroyed,
they will look for a new place to live.
Huh.
You can use the housing interface
to assign and view housing.
Open your inventory
and click the house icon.
Yo! What?
House icon?
House. House.
Wait, am I blind?
Hotbar, block, ruler.
Heavy metal.
Hum.
Housing.
Oh! Housing!
Wait.
What did you say about?
What's this? Housing query.
Sorry.
Huh?
Wait.
This room is missing a wall.
Oh, I get it!
I have assigned this house to...
to Joe now.
Look, there's a little...
Ah.
Okay.
This housing is suitable.
Joe.
This is your home.
God damn it. This is how...
I'm a benevolent friend.
I shall gift you this home that I have bought.
I mean, crafted.
Built. With my own hands.
Lots of sweat and tears went into it.
I hope you enjoy.
I am gonna build a house next to yours.
And it's gonna be...
I could also...
You know what?
It's daytime.
We should go out and explore
and find more wood.
Not that way, because there's a graveyard.
Let's go! Also, I'm gonna try and find some food.
Uh...
Don't go down there. That's a bad idea.
I love this music.
It's so cute!
It takes a while to chop these trees, doesn't it?
It takes a long while.
I know.
A bunny!
It's a white bunny!
Thank you.
I wonder if I can eat the bunny.
A bunny!
Bro, that is brutal.
I...
It fell in half.
I was not expecting that level of brutality here in this game.
But you know what?
I'm happy to see it.
I love blood.
Dude, I'm getting so much wood.
Of course I got to build a house that's better...
Ah!
Is this a new biome?
Look at that!
Oh, I like the haste effect!
Exciting!
Uh-oh!
He's very aggressive now for some reason.
Ugh!
Oh, shit.
Get up!
Ugh! Okay, I should be careful.
I need to have the food at the ready.
Nice.
And then I get this debuff.
Okay, potion sickness.
Cannot consume any more healing items.
So that's how they balance that.
You can't just spam that button.
It makes sense.
Oh, look at that!
We've got cacti over there!
Dude, I'm getting...
Oh, I get it now.
The bigger the tree is, the more wood you get.
I mean, it's kind of obvious when you say it out loud, but...
I was wondering why I only got a little wood sometimes,
but it totally makes sense.
Thank you.
God, this weapon is insane.
I wonder how I can upgrade it with torches.
I definitely want to upgrade it with torches.
Okay, let's head back. We got a lot of wood.
I'm going to take this mushroom here.
Do we need to eat it?
I should go foraging some more here, you know?
Can I chop trees with this?
No.
Hey, Joe! Oh, my God.
Joe's so happy. Look at him.
I made a home for him.
Joe!
My dude!
Yeah, you want...
You want to go fishing or do you want me to go fishing?
I realize you want to fish.
Something is about fishing.
What does this cost to make?
You know what? Let's do it.
I have two of these now!
Star power!
Awesome.
Can I just keep making those?
I'm going to make some of these as well.
Heck yeah, man.
Okay.
Joe!
You can even remove people from their home
from the housing interface.
Right-click the banner hanging in the house.
You can also left-click to assign them to a new home.
Yes!
If you want a merchant to move in,
you will need to gather plenty of money.
50 silver coins should do the trick.
How much do I have?
I have 74.
Hey!
They say there is a person
who will tell you how to survive in this land.
Yeah, that's you.
You know what?
Max will make the same joke.
For a nurse to move in,
you might want to increase your maximum life.
Gotcha!
But for now,
it's time to build a home.
Because I've got all the materials.
Actually, do I? Hold on.
Let's craft a bunch of walls first.
I do have a bunch of walls,
but I need more walls.
Let's see here.
Oh, I have a shit ton of wood!
Holy shit, I can make shit ton of wood.
200 wall.
I really like that it looks like there's no maximum stack size here.
That's awesome.
Okay, let's assign correctly here.
Wood there.
There.
I will help you!
The white bunny shall die!
Okay.
And then...
Let's make a house
for myself right here.
Oh my god, we got a thingy!
Demon eye. What is it with demons?
Everything is demonic.
Demonic maze. We have an annoying copper axe
and a demonic copper pickaxe.
Pickaxe.
Excuse me.
This here is Joe's
domicile.
Okay, he's down there now.
So that is actually fine with me because
see ya!
Let's make the flooring here.
Oh no, how do I get rid of this?
Oh, thank you.
I'm so sorry I didn't mean to do that.
Man, how do I remove that fucking thing?
Hammer?
I have zero clue.
Okay, let's not build it that close.
Also, is the axe better for this?
Okay, it's not. Looks like the pickaxe is used for
almost everything.
I think this is going to disappear after a while.
I need a bit more flooring here.
Why is that floor not complete?
I think...
The zombies all look different.
To a certain degree at least.
Also, it's kind of dark here.
Let's put down some lights.
Okay, you know what?
What is this called? A maze.
The maze is way better.
I should eat. There we go.
Dude, I'm totally mastering this game here.
We had a bit of a rough start,
but things are finally coming together.
Oh, yeah.
Let's make it to here.
I can even make multiple floors.
I should consider doing that.
I like the song that's playing right now.
What if I do this? Is this better?
Oh, this is actually... you know what?
That's actually pretty nice.
I like the way that works.
No!
Well, we took damage from that.
No, we didn't. Never mind.
Do I have any doors left?
Door, door, door, door.
Doesn't look like it.
Oh my God, look at that!
Oh, that is satisfying.
Holy crap.
Oh, no, I ran out.
Okay, it's time. Come here.
Come here, idiots.
Come on.
Hey, you!
Ah!
You fucker.
Eat that.
Dude, look at Joe. He must be terrified.
There's a zombie knocking on the door like that.
There's so many fallen stars, though.
How do we remove this in the back?
I don't understand how this system works.
Hold on.
Auto select. Is that it?
Wait, what? No, no, no.
Wait, what?
Okay, that just plays as a torch for some reason.
Bro, I have no...
Is it the hammer?
Oh, yeah, right. Okay, the hammer.
The hammer is how you do it.
I have understood.
Looks like the hammer only removes wall.
Ah, no, no, no, no, no.
Can I just...
God damn it!
Oh, it's fine.
Why are there so many fallen stars?
Is it me or do the zombies get more HP as time goes on?
That's probably what's happening.
Okay, now we need a door.
Let's quickly make this first.
There.
Quick, quick, quick, door.
Yeah, look at that.
Speedplay.
Come here.
Oh, this is not working well.
Here we go.
Dude, I'm just collecting all these fallen stars because why not?
I'm gonna go rescue Joe.
Look at him sitting in his chair. It's so cute.
Yes.
Once again, I have rescued thy sir.
Joe.
Now I'm gonna make another door.
How about the door?
I have to be here to do that.
Door.
There.
Okay, awesome.
Let me try the hammer on this.
Ah, it doesn't work.
Oh, it's the axe.
It just takes a while.
Okay, I get it now.
I see.
I see your stance.
Now we complete the floor.
Look at that. It's beautiful.
Okay, let's make a second floor here.
Can we make something cool?
Is there like a ladder of some sort?
Oh.
Wait.
Iron wall.
Iron anvil.
Use the craft items from metal bars.
Yes.
Put it there.
We should put that next to the smithy.
Or the furnace, I guess.
That's the word.
Oh, look at this.
Fuck yeah.
Wait, tin... tin...
tungsten is better.
Let's make a tungsten axe.
Fuck yeah, it's happening.
It's happening.
Oh, that's it.
That's all I had. That's okay.
That's perfect. Hey, what's up dudes?
It's the door technique.
You know what this weapon reminds me of?
It's like that thing you do with your siblings
when you're young, you know?
You're like, I'm gonna walk towards you
with my arms doing this.
And if you get hit, it's your own fault.
I don't know if you guys ever did that as a child.
There we go.
Let's kill this guy over here.
Nice.
Oliver has defeated the 50th zombie!
Awesome.
Oh, I'm getting all these.
Looks like Dawn is about to break as well.
Hey you, come here.
Zombie man.
Also, I should be eating every time I can.
Uh...
Mushroom?
Eat. Nice.
Okay, let's not go to that
biome over there just yet.
I have things to do here.
God, this weapon is amazing!
Dude, that's such a cool find!
I love shit like that!
I'm having fun so far. I'm liking this game.
Let's see how fast it is.
I mean...
It's faster, isn't it?
Yeah, it's definitely faster.
Oh yeah.
Look at that shit.
That is significantly faster.
Maybe half.
Oh yeah.
That's so nice.
Hey!
Thank you.
Okay, okay.
Joe!
Help!
If you had a gun,
I bet an arm stealer might show up
to sell you some ammo.
Really?
There's guns in this game?
You're freaking kidding me.
You should prove yourself by defeating a strong monster.
That will get the attention of a dryad.
Wait, those are like forest
things, aren't they?
Why is that a good thing?
I don't want the attention of a dryad.
Hang on to any bombs you might find.
A demolitionist may want to have a look at them.
Thanks, Joe.
You are full of wisdom.
I once met a stylist in this region.
She went off adventuring on the ground
and that was the last I saw of her.
Wonder what became of her.
I don't know, but I will find her
and rescue her, mark my words, Joe.
Now, is there anything I can assist you with today?
Can I perhaps
build you something for your house?
I don't know.
No, Joe.
Joe, that's my house.
Your house is over.
Hold on, did I not do this thing?
Yeah, see, that's
reserved for Joe the guide.
Awesome.
It's raining.
Okay, Joe, hold on.
I do have a mission to enter your house
because I built it.
The furnace comes with me. I'm sorry, but you're not using it.
Put it there.
Let's smelt some shit.
We can make chains.
Can be placed. Can be climbed on.
Flaming mace.
Wait, 18 is worse.
May the fire light your way.
Call me crazy, but isn't that
worse?
Mine cart.
No way.
You can do that?
A pink mace.
Joe, I have brought you a gift.
What do you think of that?
That's for you. You like it a lot, don't you?
Hold on.
I also have a gold chest.
I'm going to place that.
I definitely need more rooms in this house.
This is not enough room for activities.
Is there anything resembling a staircase?
I guess I could use rope.
That seems a little barbarian, doesn't it?
I need to get on top here.
Okay, nice.
Let's not make it there, actually.
Oh, you know what? I'm going to replace this with floorboards.
It doesn't make any sense to have this be a stone.
Oh, yeah, I'm seeing possibilities already.
This is cool so far. I like it.
I'm going to go in the mine as well at some point.
Not this. What's that?
Zombie banner.
Oh!
Nearby players get a bonus against zombie!
No shit!
I need to hang on something, I guess.
Why can't I...
Wait.
It can be placed.
Outside?
What am I missing here?
Okay, I don't get it.
That's okay. I'm going to figure that out later.
Acorns. Maybe I should plant some more trees.
What the fuck?
An umbrella slide!
What?!
Hey!
You don't want to get wet?
Is that... can I take that umbrella?
Whoops.
I'm so confused.
Okay, the umbrella disappears.
Discover and smash your first hard crystal on the ground.
Oh, is this like a very light sort of guide for me?
The next achievement, sort of like the advancements in Minecraft.
Okay, first of all, though...
I already have inventory problems.
I need to sort!
Oh!
Wait, I have that?
What?
A rash shackle.
Oh!
Nice!
Two percent melee speed and one defense?
That's not bad.
What else do I have?
A lens!
Can I make a telescope?
Yellow marigold.
Used to make yellow die.
Okay.
Where did my flooring go?
Ah.
Wait, no, is this it?
It is!
This is how we do it.
Like that.
And then we make a little hole.
Let's make it sort of...
I don't even know, like...
But how am I going to get up is the question.
What if I just make a...
Do the naive thing here?
Oops, that's not the right one.
Put this here.
What if I go like that?
Wait, wait, wait!
Hold on, I know what to do.
Excuse me, Joe!
I need to break up your floor.
What are you saying?
You want to run?
I'll be right back.
They had staircases down here.
I need to see how they did it.
Ah!
I'm stealing that.
Also, what is that?
A horrible night for alchemy.
Huh?
What? Oh, platform!
Okay, okay, okay.
I understand.
I understand!
Ah, look at that.
Didn't I also make a bunch of this?
Wait, I had way more.
I had a million of this.
I guess it disappeared.
But I can make more.
I can make more of that.
No problem.
Oh, god, this is a little bit awkward.
Ah!
Oh, this is way faster.
Oh, wait, it's the same speed, never mind.
Actually, I don't know.
Maybe it's the different speed.
Joe is once again stuck down here.
I don't know.
I'm so sorry, Joe.
This is how it's going to be from now on.
A whore...
W black.
Is that a reference to Walter White,
but like the opposite?
I feel like I should make this floor one higher,
just so this doesn't look weird.
Ah, let's see.
Oh!
Oh, never mind. I thought there was a guy over here.
It's just this silly thing.
Thank you.
What is that flying fish?
Glowstick.
Why are you raving fish?
Oh, cool.
Oh, I can't pick it up again.
Shit.
I should have saved that.
Wait, what is happening here?
Oh, it's opening the chest
because I had the thingy. Look.
It's like an automatic selector type deal.
I get it. I get it.
So I can place things in here.
I guess, let's place some...
some random shit
that I don't know what to do with yet in here.
Also, the annoying copper axe goes in there
because it's annoying.
Lens goes in there.
Work, sure.
Yes, that's okay.
The copper she goes in here
because that sucks.
Maybe... can I give that to Joe, I wonder?
I was thinking... loadout.
Grappling hook.
Mount.
Oh, my God.
Oh, it's about to thunder.
I wonder what that means.
Wait, why can't I remove that?
Oh, okay. I need to be one higher.
I was not high enough
to make this one taller.
And we build up like that.
And... let's see here.
Such dramatic music.
I put this...
Ah, man, I...
I need to be a little higher up.
This is very dramatic right now.
What's with the music and the weather right now?
I get the feeling something's gonna happen here.
Nope, I won't.
Yes, look at that.
Now, if that isn't beautiful, then I don't know what is.
And then we're gonna keep going like that.
Look at that!
Let me try this.
Okay, so it's like automatically doing things I don't want it to do.
That's okay.
Look at that!
Beautiful stuff right there.
If I do say so myself.
What if I use it like that?
Okay, that's actually...
That's decently smart.
I should have made it one higher though.
I just realized.
And with the platforms now...
Let's make it...
Like this.
Like that.
Look at that!
Let's see, let's make a bunch more.
Oh wait, this one is in the way now.
Damn it.
Look!
Isn't there a better way of doing this?
Can I go like this maybe?
Isn't that what they did down there?
Remove it.
And then...
Like that.
And then I can walk like this. Look at that!
And then I can drop down.
That's how you do it, baby.
And that's also what counts as a trap door, I guess.
That's what I need to be building over here.
Let's make more.
It's trap door time, baby.
In fact, just make a bunch. I have so much wood.
Can I shift click this to make it faster?
Let's make 17.
I like this music.
Very nice.
Move that. And then we're gonna do this.
Look at this here, Joe.
Look at that!
You like it?
Wait, this is not how I envisioned it.
And this...
Like, wait, wait.
This is confusing now.
Why don't we just not continue up?
Ah, there we go.
Okay, look at that!
That's how we do it.
Why does that look so weird?
There we go.
Beautiful stuff. We can even make it a little further down like that.
Nope.
There, there.
Look at that, Joe.
Yeah, Joe is back, baby!
Nice.
Okay, things are happening.
Let's put torches.
Let's do a torch there.
And a torch there.
And we're gonna have a torch there.
And then a torch there.
Look at that.
This is a home.
Actually a home.
Now, how do I easily get up there
to remove these noises?
There we go.
No!
Shit!
Man, the hammer is confusing me.
Like, it's not removing things.
It's...
I mean, it is removing,
but it's also modifying a little bit.
And I'm not sure I understand.
Keen wooden hammer.
Nice.
I'll figure that out later.
Oh, God. Fuck!
I need to just get up here so I can stand here.
This must be painful to look at. I'm sorry.
I apologize
for the silliness.
There we go.
And now we can place this. There it is!
Beautiful.
I also realized that I should maybe
have made this one taller.
So I can have the same height here.
But I do like it the way it is.
So if I have to walk through it like this,
I have to hold down to keep walking.
Got it.
Look at that! He has a raincoat on.
Door technique.
Oh shit, I'm dying.
I need to eat.
Bro, there are many enemies.
I have...
I need to make more crazy arrows here.
Crazy arrows.
Fuck yeah, look at that!
I'm gonna...
How am I gonna do this?
Go from the top.
Like this.
Hey bastards!
Get off my property!
This is private property!
Oliver and Joe only.
No demons.
No creepy eyes.
Okay, here we go.
I'm gonna make a drop attack here.
Eat this.
Hey!
Hey, you like that?
Huh?
I bet you hate it!
I know you hate that.
Okay, that's satisfying.
Okay.
What should I be doing here?
Let's see, crafting.
Let me actually finish the roof here.
I need a fast way to get up and down here.
So let's make a little keybind.
Let's have dirt on...
Let's say this keybind there.
Such that I can do this.
Ah, you bastard!
Oh, wait what?
I like this soundtrack.
It's super fitting.
I can't explain why,
but it just fits.
You know?
Thank you.
Okay.
Can I please have some peace now?
I am building my house.
I need this one toler.
And I also need...
to ascend.
Oh! I wonder if there's full damage.
Eat that.
Man, oh, you know what I should make?
I should make a bed.
Probably I can skip the night.
Why didn't I think of this?
Oh man, the inventory is...
hard to get used to here.
Hold on.
Get off of me.
There it is.
Gimme.
Okay.
Sort inventory.
That's actually pretty cool how it
highlights with different colors what's what.
I'm liking that.
Didn't I have some standard woods somewhere?
Just normal wooden things?
Oh, there.
Okay, build it one higher this time.
So it's like...
Oh wait, I can use this?
Wait a minute.
Ruler.
10, that's 13.
7, 1, 2, 3.
So that's like 4.
6 needs to go to there.
Cool.
A little confusing.
How that works.
I shall take it.
Look at that!
And then I'm going to make the ladder
go this way now.
Should I know? Is that smart?
Actually, no, no. I'm going to make it go like this again.
That's genius.
Then we remove these.
And then we put platforms there.
Platforms...
Look at that!
Man, the learning is...
Wait.
Wait, this is not going according to plan.
Why is it doing that?
Hey, you...
Platform?
There?
I'm confused!
No, no, it's too much to the left here.
It's bad.
Oh, shit.
Oh, wait. I think I need wall.
Oh.
Maybe it needs to be attached to the wall.
That's what it is, I think.
No, no, no, no, no.
Oh, I'm terrible at this game. Holy shit.
Okay.
This one now.
Why is that not laddering?
Wait, I'm so...
Oh, I'm losing my mind.
Sir, why do you not ladder?
Why are you not laddering?
I'm scared of the ladder.
Too many enemies, too high-scaled.
People are scared of the ladder.
Here.
It's dark craft, that is.
Okay, hold on.
Maybe I need to remove this up here.
Get rid of that shit for now.
It's gonna confuse the game.
Make one here.
Make one there.
Let's activate this.
Okay, okay.
Bro, this is the hardest thing ever.
There.
Except it's one too much to the right.
Fuck me.
I think it's better if we start from the bottom
and work our way up.
How about that?
So here's what I'm gonna do.
I'm gonna mirror this construction here.
This is how I do it.
There.
And then...
No. Go up.
Why won't you go up?
This makes zero fucking sense.
And won't you guys shut the fuck up down there?
I'm trying to work.
Got...
Damn.
I've had enough of you.
Fuck off.
Get off my property.
Okay.
Now.
Put this there.
Activate this.
There.
No.
It's almost...
Why is it not working?
Is it because of this?
Is that the issue?
Hold on.
Let's try the...
Can I even walk like this though?
Let's say I walk up like that.
No, I get stuck.
Okay. One more.
There.
Let's see now.
And... and...
Yes!
There it is.
Okay.
I finally did it. That was a hard one.
God damn.
I shouldn't remove that actually. That was some of me.
I need to make one more like that.
No, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Remove that.
Place the wall there.
And then...
Here.
I get why the music is dramatic now.
It really fits the game when you're building stairs like this.
It's a boss fight.
That's what it is.
Building stairs, man.
Oh, shit.
Give me the wall. No!
The flying fish is attacking me.
How dare you.
I'm running low on food here.
I...
Yeah, we're gonna make one more story and then that's it.
We gotta stop the fun at some point here.
Is that...
I think one more.
Yeah, that looks right.
I can also stand on this. I just realized.
We're mine crafting now.
Like that. And then we actually use this for the roof.
Oh, we don't have enough.
That's fine.
Oh.
Get out of here.
Fuck it, we're gonna use this as roof.
Doesn't matter.
Oh, this is actually pretty sick.
The way you don't have to switch items.
There it is.
Now I need to get inside.
Okay, it looks like I don't take fall damage.
That's neat.
Now, we're almost there.
Yes.
Why is the music so dramatic?
I actually don't understand what's happening.
Is it just the weather?
I need to make a bit more wall here.
Can I do this quicker somehow?
No matter.
Let me try this again.
Ah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's nice.
Look at that.
And then...
There.
And there.
Would you look at this amazing looking house?
Actually, the furnace is fine down here.
Put it like there.
That's fine.
Okay.
This one can go here, because why not?
Look at that.
Beautiful.
Upstairs should be like a storage.
Oh, can I...
Can you see this?
Ah, okay.
I see, I see.
Storage area upstairs.
There.
Let's put some stuff in there again.
Very nice.
Look at this organization.
I think it's time to head out
and kill some shit. That's a goldfish.
What is it with fish not being
in water in this game?
Okay.
We're venturing out.
We have no fear.
Give me mushroom.
In fact, we should equip the mushroom.
Yeah.
Let's go. Need more mushrooms.
What's this?
Alright, demon eye thing.
Man, this weapon slaps.
Yep, yep.
Thank you.
It's so cute that the zombies
have overalls on.
Raincoats.
Okay.
Let's go somewhere, huh?
Let's find a powerful enemy.
Uh-oh.
That looks scary.
Let's see here.
Whoa!
What's this?
Strong zombie arm.
50 melee damage.
50% knockback.
55% axe power?
I don't know what that means.
I kind of want to try it.
Yes.
Let me try it on this.
Hey you.
Oh, that's very overwhelming.
I think I'd definitely prefer my...
my mace.
Oh god.
Let me just take care of this guy first.
There we go.
Yeah!
Another glow stick!
Let's put that in there.
Man, this thing right here is the tits.
I'm loving that.
Okay.
Rope?
See, here's the thing. Check this out.
No, wait.
Is that a good idea?
I mean, I guess I could just build a platform.
To get across here.
What if I do this though?
Uh, sorry.
Will you go away?
Thank you.
Oh.
I thought I could maybe swing across.
Didn't quite go as expected there.
I'm going to make a platform.
Because why not?
That is... no, that's clay.
Do we have dirt?
With you.
Guys, get out of here.
You fell down.
Yeah, this is super easy. Let's just do that.
There's no reason to overthink this.
Oh.
What is this?
Recall potion.
Teleport you home!
Dude.
Hell yeah.
Lead bar.
And shit ton of glow sticks.
And a strong spear.
Can I open this as well?
Bomb!
Oh shit.
Uh...
Didn't he say something about holding onto bombs?
Someone would like to take a look at them.
Joe, that is.
I can go down here as well.
See, that's interesting.
What does that mean?
Should I do that?
Try it.
Ooh, there's platforms.
I should make platforms on my way down.
See, this is the smart play right here.
This is the thousand IQ play.
And I can get up like that.
You see that?
Look at that.
Ooh, what did we got here?
Uh, make it like that.
Okay.
Make one here.
No, no, no, no.
Ooh, this is deep.
We're going deep, boys.
Nope.
Oh, okay.
Okay.
Platform there.
Look at this weird-ass door.
Less the healing potion.
There's stuff up there as well.
A bomb!
Dude, I gotta try the bomb.
There's so many goodies here.
Let's see here.
A small explosion that will destroy most tiles.
Okay.
Put it there.
Cool!
I like that.
That's awesome.
Yo, I'm getting all kinds of things here.
What is this music?
I don't know why.
This game just makes me smile.
What's that?
Looks like bones.
Oh, that's not high enough.
Shit.
Let me remove that.
Make it nice and neat.
Oof.
No.
That way we can...
Oh, it's not high enough.
Mm-hmm.
There we go.
I wonder if there's a door in this game.
Wait, why can't I enter here?
Oh!
What's that?
Oh, it's dripping something evil.
Evil things.
There's evil in the living wood door.
Bombs, yes.
Living would want.
Sure.
Okay, I think it's part of the music.
Living loom?
Why is it dripping blood?
What's happening?
Oh!
Of course, of course.
Oh, wait.
Huh, look at this.
This weapon has so much utility.
It's incredible.
It's dripping blood or something.
And I don't like it.
Also, my inventory is crazy full.
How do I...
There.
Sort that shit.
Oh, here we go.
Now we got music.
Okay, hold on.
How many... is this one?
I can't count this.
I need to know this for the future.
It's just like 1, 2, 3, 4,
5...
5 in between.
Okay.
So that way it's always...
it always needs to be 5.
So I can make this jump.
What was that?
1, 2, 3, 4...
I think 5 there.
Yeah.
Hopefully that will become second nature at some point.
Look at that.
Oh, I'm going deep.
It's getting dark as well.
This is scary.
And the good part is,
even if I get lost, I have a thingy to get home.
Somewhere I have a thingy to get home.
Like that.
Is that another bone?
Oh, we've got something.
A snail.
We snail in now.
Is it an enemy? Let's test.
It's not. But can I eat you?
20.
I need to make more.
Oh, shit.
We are going to make a lot of those.
This seems like the most
utility thing ever.
Nice, nice.
Look at that.
Like that.
We're going deep.
There's something in there.
Hold on a sec.
We're making a detour.
Things are happening and there's caves.
Look at this.
The utility strikes.
Never mind.
It looks like you cannot make the stairs
when you're not in the smart function.
If I activate smart,
then you can do it.
You need to be in this mode.
Otherwise it just won't work.
Look at that. Getting some practice
with the stairs here.
I'm hearing enemies.
Uh-oh.
Oh!
What is that?
That looks like a detonator
for that piece of TNT
right over there.
And what is this kind of
thing there?
I'm trying to activate it.
I got a detonator!
It can be placed.
The guts and
gory.
That's the joke, isn't it?
Looks like there's breath.
It's really dark
if you don't have a torch.
What's happening with the background here?
That looks evil to me.
Do we have evil here?
That looks evil.
A salamander.
A lot of HP.
Uh-oh.
Someone's coming!
What's that?
Silver? Nice.
What is that over there?
Salamander?
Excuse me, sir. You must be evil.
Oh, you spitting shit at me!
Okay, that's a lot of HP.
Holy crap, I need to eat
right now.
What is this?
Tin.
Oh my God, my inventory!
I gotta throw some shit away.
Let's see. What do I not need?
Let's throw away this.
Alright.
Let's have a little spot where we can...
What is that?
Hold on.
Let's throw it down here.
So we're gonna throw that.
A little further like that.
Day bloom.
Sure.
Throw that shit away.
Crimson torch.
I don't want it.
I don't know what it does, so I don't understand it,
so I hate it.
Am I?
Clay block?
Throw that away.
This is the exact same problem
as Minecraft.
How do I delete things?
Can I delete things?
Oh wait, I can delete things!
Wait.
Why is that not working?
Does it take a while?
Whoa!
Quick stack to nearby chests.
That's an amazing feature.
Holy shit.
Let me wait a bit.
We've got enemies.
Oh, look at that. Blue jellyfish!
Hey, jelly...
Jelly!
Nice.
Piranha.
That's bad.
Bro, this weapon right here
is carrying me so hard right now.
Imagine if I didn't have this weapon.
Imagine that.
Um...
How does this fucking work?
What am I...
Hold on.
I don't get it.
Maybe only some things can be...
Trying to press buttons on this.
What the fuck?
There's something I'm missing here.
You know what?
My inventory is shit right now.
It's time for me to head home.
Let me try this.
Nice!
Okay, so that puts me where I spawned, I guess.
This is where I spawn in the world.
Cool.
Get rid of these fools.
Oh yeah, compared to the beginning
I am fucking flying through this game right now.
Wait, what?
What was that in here?
Did we just have cobwebs in here?
I'm not sure.
I like that.
What's that all about?
Can I destroy my own house?
Hmm.
Okay.
It's time to put shit in the chests.
Let's try this.
That was a button.
Oh wait, I have to have something in here, I guess.
Living loom.
Used for special crafting.
Let's put it somewhere.
Let's put that there.
Why not?
And then we have a living wood door.
You know what?
Why not?
Let's place that shit.
Hey you.
You mind fucking off?
Wait, I need to make another...
Oh, and I'm looking away.
You fucker.
Eat.
And then I need this.
Nope, I need this.
There.
Now we utilize the door there.
Look at that!
Beautiful.
That way I can get out of here, up there.
So I can jump down these fools and kill them.
Okay.
Next.
I have a wand.
Places living wood.
Wait, like a spell?
Is that a spell wand?
Harry Potter?
Wait.
Consumes places leaves.
Let's put another chest down, I guess.
This is the storage room.
Oh, I know what to do, bro.
Hey! Hey fools!
What do you think of that?
Oh wait, that's going to destroy the ground.
That's not good.
I have regrets.
Of course it's going to do that.
Let me go help Joe out a little bit here.
No! I didn't notice my HP.
Goddamn!
I dropped some money.
Three gold 49 copper.
I wonder if one gold is 100 silver
and one silver is 100 copper?
Let's see, how much do I have on me now?
I still have some gold on me.
So you don't drop everything.
Now, it's kind of annoying to have to go out
through a door when there's a zombie because
they will fuck you up.
Oh my god.
Okay, that's better, that's better.
It's working.
Okay, beautiful.
Lens, let me go help Joe out.
I lost seeing those damage numbers.
That makes me happy.
Joe!
You should stay indoors at night.
It is very dangerous to be wandering around in the dark.
Help!
Ever caught a strange fish
and you aren't sure what to do with it?
I hear a fishing master lives near the ocean.
Might have a use for those.
Ah.
Thanks, Joe!
You always filled...
What's this?
No, can I remove this shit?
We don't want to...
Good.
I don't want to remember these deaths.
These go in the forgetting book.
As they say.
Actually, nobody says that.
Hey!
It has horns.
Okay.
Now,
let's go sort some items here.
This is always my issue in games.
Here's what I'm going to do.
I'm going to sort like this first.
And then sort by...
I do want to try these out.
Fishing pole lens.
This puts all kinds of shit.
This is the miscellaneous chest, as you can tell.
I have gold and I have all kinds of things.
Gills potion.
Breathe water instead of air.
Does that mean I...
I'm going to actually run out of breath
when I'm not in water?
Imagine that.
Let's see what we can make.
Mana crystal.
Yeah, why not?
We have three now.
60 mana in total.
We need the crafting bench.
Did I put that in the chest?
I probably did, didn't I?
Crafting bench.
Iron anvil. We need that again.
And we need this.
Yes.
The bottom floor is the crafting floor.
Because it makes sense.
Wait.
What did...
Oh!
Oh! Never mind.
I'm an idiot.
I get it.
And then we have this.
That goes next to...
Sure, put it there.
Okay. Let's see now.
Crafting.
I can make a wither vein.
Let's do it. Four bars.
And we can make a tungsten bow.
Tungsten helmet.
I think...
I think we may have to go with the defense here.
A small explosion that will spread dirt.
And this is a small explosion that will destroy most tiles.
Tossing may be difficult.
But it's sticky.
Oh, the bow though.
The bow could be nice.
How much is my current one?
Four! Oh, that's a sick upgrade.
I got it. I got it. I got it.
I got to make it.
How does this work?
I don't... I don't get it.
I don't get it.
Why is this not being destroyed?
No knockback.
Okay, what else can I make?
I don't know if I should make this.
This seems worse.
Doesn't it?
It seems like a worse one.
So that's a bad idea.
You can make silver coins?
You just make your own money.
I feel like that's...
a bit crazy, isn't it?
Gold bars?
Let's do it.
Maybe I can craft something with that.
Like a candle.
Yes, let's make a candle.
We should make a table in here as well, actually.
I have wood, don't I?
Did I put that in the chest?
Let's put the wood back in here.
The wood is nice to have.
Can I also put this
outside to make it look nice?
What?
They blew material. Oh, okay.
I guess I can't.
At least not right now.
I need table.
Workbench.
Wait, I can make more tungsten.
Tungsten hammer maybe?
Why not?
Let's just upgrade all the things we can, right?
There's no reason not to.
And what's this?
Living wood stuff.
Living wood dresser.
Candelabra.
Ooh, that's a nice looking workbench.
I wonder if this will allow me to create
new items.
A toilet?
Living wood toilet?
I don't know why that caught me off guard.
I did not expect to be able to
make toilets in this game.
I am very surprised by that.
Discovery.
Why can't I make a normal ass toilet?
I don't want plants up in my ass.
Table.
Let's put the table.
Can I not put it here?
I can't, okay.
Man, I'm realizing here.
My houses need to be bigger.
There's not enough room for this.
There's just not.
We need more.
In fact, there's not room for anything.
I'm gonna put this table here.
And then have a chair on each side.
We can't have this guy, Joe, over here,
have a superior table
set up than we have, right?
Let's make two of these.
And then... there.
How do I...
No, no, no, no.
Why rotate?
Oh, it just did it automatically there.
There's gotta be a keybind to do that, though.
Coin sample. Discover and smash your first heart crystal underground.
I will do that at some point.
For sure, but now look at this.
Look at this.
Tell me that's not superior to Joe.
Joe has a torch.
I have a candle.
That, my friends,
is superiority.
Uh, you know what?
Joe, how do you feel about this?
You want that?
That's for you.
You deserve it for being such a nice guide.
In this game.
This restore is 50 life.
That could be very useful in combat, actually.
Ralph, the merchant has arrived?
Where?
Ralph.
Wait, does that mean...
Ralph?
Ralph.
We are gonna...
I'm gonna make you a house.
In fact, I know exactly...
I know exactly what to do.
We're gonna make a little bit of a...
You're gonna be on the second floor here, buddy.
Shit, not like that.
Come on, hurry.
I can't reach!
Minecraft.
Let's go. Ralph!
Hang on, buddy. I got you.
House coming right up!
And then this.
Cool.
No!
Joe, go say hi to our guest.
An esteemed trader has arrived in town.
He shall be welcomed.
So what did I say?
I needed a chair, a torch and something else.
A table, I think.
And walls.
Okay, so now I'm gonna do this.
Man, look how fast I'm gonna do this now.
I have learned everything.
I'm gonna do like that.
I wonder if I can move him in upstairs.
Is this gonna count as a separate one?
That's the question here.
Ralph!
I got you, buddy!
What the heck?
Oh, I didn't mean to drink that, but okay.
Awesome.
Ralph, we're gonna set you up up here.
So we're gonna use this now.
And let's see.
There's already one here, so I say there now.
There.
Look.
Oh, no.
This is very confusing.
Okay, that's it, that's it.
And now, remove this.
And then, yes!
And there it is.
Easily done.
Then we need another wall.
Look, I'm not even moving my mouse.
It's doing it automatically.
That's actually pretty cool.
It's smart enough to know that
I want to only build it in here.
Yeah, it's not that smart.
It started to make stairs now for some reason.
Ralph is already moving in!
Ralph, this chair is for you!
We're even gonna have a table for you, buddy.
Hold on, I'll be right back.
I just need to see here.
This house is missing a light source and a...
Okay, okay, okay, okay now.
Table coming right up.
Table.
Let's see.
One of these.
Light source I have.
Okay, Ralph.
You like mining!
Me too!
Ralph!
Is he singing? Oh, he's scared.
Dolgen the demolitionist!
No, no.
Light will be upon us soon, friend.
Make your choices while you...
What?
Oh, I think I actually clicked on him there.
Ralph, this is for you.
That's your place!
Oh my god, I need to make more now.
We've got people coming in!
What was he called? Dolgen!
Dolgen, where are you?
Dolgen!
Buddy!
What's up?
Check out my goods!
They have explosive prices!
Happiness.
I don't have a place to live. Did I blow up my last one?
Ah, no one around.
I can test new bombs without creating a graveyard for limbs!
Okay.
Shop?
You sell dynamite?
Bombs and grenades, huh?
Wait.
I don't fucking get this.
Wait, I can sell this?
Oh!
I see.
Oh, he would pay a lot for this, no?
Maybe I'll use that.
That's for me.
If I can buy dynamite, I can probably use that in conjunction with the detonator.
Okay, Dolgen!
One house coming right up!
I'm gonna make you on top of here!
I'm getting good at this.
Let's do one...
Here's the question now.
I think I have to remove...
Let's see if I can do this first try without fucking it up.
I make one here.
There.
Wait, no, no, no, no.
It needs to be one...
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
It needs to be one higher.
It's like...
There.
Actually, is that fine?
Something ain't right here.
Why is it doing that?
I mean, it almost looks correct.
Is it, though?
Is this correct?
Why does this look wrong?
Is that how we do it?
No, no, it's one too much to the right.
Fuck!
Well, I almost did it.
So now we go...
Let me start from up here, actually.
We're ascending.
And then let's remove this.
And then we go here.
Here, look at that. There's how we do it.
I'm nailing it.
It's happening.
Yes!
Ralph, move!
Move!
No!
It's already not working again.
There. Yes, and now...
There it is.
Man, the stairs are...
insanely difficult to make.
Wow!
Like that.
I mean, it's a little bit...
samey, I realize.
It's okay.
As long as they have a place to live, right?
It's all that matters.
We can make improvements later.
Nope, I need this.
There.
And then remove...
No, no, no, no. There we go.
Let's see if I can do this first try.
Okay.
Here.
Here. There.
There.
Wait.
Now we have to remove it like that.
Let me do three just to be safe here.
There.
And...
Look! First try.
I'm proud of that.
I'm getting good at this.
Fuck yeah.
Yeah.
Stone block.
And then we need some wall, don't we?
Did I bring that?
Nope, I did not.
I got a swan I did though.
Uh, Dolgen.
This is not your home.
Oh, you know what? I probably used my wall.
I don't have any left.
Oh, right.
Um,
make some wall.
Can I shift?
Can I...
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
I understand.
I get it.
That's way better.
Just hold the damn button.
Yeah, you use a lot of wall.
More than you would think.
See, the automatic one is not 100%.
It's not trustworthy, I don't think.
It does stuff like that.
And manually...
do the rest.
Have a light source here.
And then we need a table and a chair.
Let's vary it a little bit this time.
And by varying it, I do mean...
Is it this one?
What do we got?
Living with dresser...
Living with table.
Let's make one of these.
Let's make a living with chair as well.
Because why not?
That's going to be for Dolgen.
And we're going to make a big variation here.
The table will be on the right this time.
That looks neat. How do I...
I need to figure out how to rotate these things.
Let me pick up these.
In fact...
Dolgen?
That's for you, buddy!
I'll go.
Also, what do you do? Ralph?
Did you say gold? Let's take that off you.
Happiness.
This is nice. Lots of privacy to store my wares.
I like the scenery in the forest.
A good view attracts customers.
Sure. What do you sell, though?
A forest pylon.
Teleport to another pylon when two villagers are nearby.
You can only place one per type and in the matching biome.
Huh.
Interesting.
Are we technically in forest right now?
Wooden arrows. You make potions.
A bug net!
I'll take it off your hands.
A piggy bank.
Can be used to store your items.
Can only be accessed by you.
Hmm. Mining helmet.
Provides light when worn?
Three gold. Oh, that's expensive.
But I want it.
Oh, yeah, baby.
Oh, yo, that's amazing.
I love that. It's even better with defense, too.
That's awesome.
Okay.
Ralph.
I hope a scrawny kid like you isn't all that is standing between us.
And Cthulhu's eye.
I actually don't know what this means.
I've heard this many times.
It's a type of enemy, isn't it?
I think it's a reference to something.
But I'm not sure what Cthulhu means.
And at this point, I'm too afraid to ask, you know?
Zombie dude, you need to take a chill pill here.
Get away from me.
Give me that.
No!
I should have used my bug in it.
It was a frog.
Let's get it ready.
Replace it with bombs.
Make love, not war.
Iron skin potion.
I already had one of those before and I used it.
So here's the thing. Let's test something.
Let's remove some of these gravestones and see if the graveyard persists.
There we go!
Yeah, we don't want these gravestones here.
Oliver was put in a glass coffin by a zombie.
Jump on me!
You can totally stagger them if you get into a nice little attack there.
Okay.
Oliver got murked by demon eye.
And that's a ghost.
Uh oh.
Yeah! Monarch butterfly! I got it!
I don't know why I'm so excited. I don't know what it does, but it makes me happy.
Zombie!
Okay, I feel like they're gaining more HP.
This is a different feeling than the beginning. I think they get stronger with time.
Let's try and pay attention. They have like 90 HP now.
Man, look at my little village!
It's so nice.
Oliver's body was mangled, but I don't like all these descriptions of what happened.
I have different memories of what happened.
I wasn't mangled.
5% bait power!
Wait.
Requires bait to catch fish!
Hold on.
You know what? Is it dawning?
I want to go fish.
We should put all these gravestones in a chest.
Let's put them up here.
This is not creepy at all.
No, I put it in here.
Gravestones.
Didn't I have more?
Weather vane!
Let's put that up there somewhere.
I can't actually...
See, this is a bit annoying.
Nice.
Weather vane.
Nice!
Looks good.
I should probably make a proper roof at some point.
I don't know how I would do that though.
Oh, there's the tombstone.
Put it in here.
Wait, what is quick stack?
Doesn't do anything?
The posset hole.
I love this feature of sorting.
Such a nice feature.
Okay, now I have to...
Okay.
It's dawn time.
Let's go fish.
Let's find a body of water and go to town.
Ralph?
Are you sure you should be out there?
There's enemies of out.
Also, you know what?
Let's go empty the inventory before we go out.
The birds.
The birds are squawking.
Maybe I'll bring the bombs.
Put the rope in...
You know what?
The bars can go in this one.
This is kind of crap.
Whoa, it disappeared!
It just takes a while, I guess.
Which is weird.
No, no.
I must have misunderstood how this works.
There's no way.
Gold goes in here.
Sure, detonator sure.
The rope coil?
I don't know.
This is the miscellaneous.
Let's put miscellaneous shit in here.
They blooms and...
I don't even know what else.
I gotta try out my new bow as well.
Gel!
Both tasty and flammable!
Nice.
Strong spear, don't want it.
Do I want it?
Wait, I can sell this shit, can I?
Okay.
Hey, Mr. Dude! Mr. Salesman!
You!
Ralph!
You like stuff like this, don't you?
That's for you, buddy.
Enjoy.
Maybe I should start selling things
instead of just storing them.
Alright, fine.
Let's go see if we can't do some fishing.
Ooh, wait.
This is probably not the spot for fishing.
I see a lake over there, why can't I fish here?
I'm gonna go even more to the left this time.
We're going a lot to the left
this time.
Also, I am curious how
how this game works
when it comes to exploration.
Is it just left and right?
Because that seems a little crazy.
Bunny!
Come here.
That works!
I was not expecting that to work.
Consumable?
Why am I shaking the bunny?
Don't shake the bunny.
I want to eat the bunny.
Get out of there, slimes.
Ah, I should have...
It's V, okay.
I will remember this.
It's a cardinal.
Cardinal.
Wait.
Never mind, I don't know what that means.
Doesn't that mean red actually?
Cardinal.
Which would make sense
because the bird is red.
Yo!
What the fuck?
Vines grew on this!
That's cool!
There's flowers on these vines too.
Okay.
Man, this is a big ass tree.
Beep beep boop boop.
Yellow marigold. I don't know if I want that.
Oh, what is that?
Face monster.
I don't know about this, bro.
Yeah.
Yeah, I don't know, man.
Yeah, you like that?
Oh!
Wait, did I just get HP from killing?
Oh, this is...
I don't know about you,
but I don't think this is the place to go fishing.
What is that?
Cremera.
Uh oh.
Alright.
Fuck you.
Look at me. I'm pro at this game now.
The combat is second nature to me.
I'm telling you.
No more deaths in this game from now on.
Wait, I'm taking damage from that.
We should also have some stuff here to eat.
Vertebra!
Drink that shit.
Okay, it's coming, it's coming.
God damn it.
Let's try this.
Ooh!
Purple slime.
Come here, come here!
You fucker!
I'll see how much damage this does.
Do I feel a difference?
Maybe?
Yeah, dude!
This is working really well.
Let's see what's up here.
I kind of want to dig down, too, but...
I'm just curious, you know?
Uh oh.
Oh.
Oh no!
That was a lot of damage!
Oh shit!
I was caught in a bad spot there.
Yep.
That's on me.
I fucked that up.
Look at that gravestone.
It's a different looking gravestone.
Alright, it's revenge time.
I've had enough of these fools.
Goddamn.
All I want to do is fish.
Handle!
The die trader has arrived.
Must build the house!
Actually...
What's this fuck?
Slimes on balloons.
Alright, well...
What is this music now?
What is happening?
Off the way the balloon goes.
I want the balloon.
I wonder if I can float.
What the fuck is that?
Angry dandelion?
What?
Why is it angry?
Oh no!
I'm actually dying here.
Fucking dying to a dandelion.
Okay.
It definitely looks like the world is getting a little scary right now.
Also, it does look like...
I cannot consume any more healing items.
Okay, so potions...
have a longer...
debuff.
Yeah, you know what actually?
You can hang out in my house.
Wait!
He moved in on his own? Or she?
I don't know if that's a female male name.
I don't know.
Sure.
Die traitor, huh?
What about my house then?
In fact, what about... oh, Joe the guide is over here.
Okay.
That's fine. You can hang out there.
I don't mind.
This is pretty nice.
What's that? Ladybug?
Give me that.
Hey!
Easy.
Squirrel.
This works on everything.
Let's shake the squirrel.
Always shake your squirrels, people.
Oh no! I missed the cardinal.
I need to check out this...
guy over here who shoots things.
Where's he?
Is it that one?
Angry dandelion.
Wait, it's gone, I think.
Oh, dandelion.
Give me that.
Probably Hano will pay good money for that.
That's a die item, isn't it?
What's this?
Dirt.
Oh, it's... never mind.
What if I shoot it?
It dies.
That kind of makes sense.
Thank you.
Can I stack bunnies?
Always stack your bunnies, people.
A vicious mushroom.
Let me eat that.
Bring it on.
Don't get close to it.
Oh, there's a lot of HP, though.
I don't know about this, dude.
Why am I here? What am I doing?
I just want to fish.
Why can't the man just fish?
Fish.
Get him.
Am I taking damage? No.
Oh, look, that's a baby one.
Get it.
Man, this boat is slapping right now.
Shot him down.
What's that?
Wait, never mind. Everything's fine.
Now can I destroy this bullshit?
Yes, I can.
I love that effect.
Or the sound effect of when getting hit.
It's just the best.
Oh, man, that's a lot of HP.
Thank you.
Uh-oh.
You know what? Let's just keep moving.
Oh, no, vicious mushroom.
I should be careful here.
Oh, when they jump, it's actually scary.
You will die from that.
Okay, the bow is superior right now.
I can't jump into it.
That's a bad idea.
What's that?
It's a stone.
It makes sense.
No, not that.
Nope, nope, nope.
No, no, no, no, no.
Don't hit it.
Oh, I hate that.
I hate that so much.
Oh, no.
Come on.
Thank God for these arrows.
They are slapping right now.
Heal up.
I can't eat either.
Okay, okay.
Don't jump on me.
Oh, no. I think I'm dead here.
I think I'm dead here.
Okay, just go, just go, just go.
Oh, why am I walking into that?
Leave, leave, leave.
Just leave me alone.
Get in here.
Okay, heal.
Eat that.
Keep digging.
It's going swimmingly so far.
I don't trust that.
Okay, wall that shit off.
Okay.
Just wait a bit here, heal up.
Get our bearings.
Wait, did I make a better pickaxe?
No, I made an axe.
Fuck.
I should have made a better pickaxe.
I realized my mistake.
What is that?
That is gravel.
Crimson block.
That's not good.
Death wheat.
Oh, I don't like the names of all these things.
Crimson?
Where?
Why can't I see it? Am I blind?
There. Crimson block.
Okay.
We have to go around that, I think.
Or we can, can I quickly replace?
No.
We got to go below it.
Oh, this is actually a little scary.
Do I take damage from blinds?
No.
Just do that.
Also, we got to eat again.
No, we don't actually. Why did I just do that?
Fuck.
You know what? I do have
potions on me if I need to go get back.
So everything is actually fine.
I do see a cave below me. Let's go.
Let's explore the caves.
We've got falling stars and shit.
What is this down here?
Oh, this is not getting destroyed.
It's some kind of a
indestructible block.
Or tile, I should say.
There is one thing I will say, though.
I do wish they would maybe
tone it down a bit with the music.
You know, give me a couple minutes without anything.
It's like the complete opposite of Minecraft.
In Minecraft, you're like, please, sir,
can I have some more music?
Here it's like complete opposite.
Let's... I'm taking that.
Maybe this is what I should be doing.
Just digging down and
grabbing materials.
Different
blocks and stuff, you know.
Do I want to go down there?
That looks like blood to me.
Seems like a bad idea.
Okay, I have an idea.
Consumers. We're going back.
And then I'm actually going to go caving.
Here.
Because I don't know about all that
red crimson shit.
That scares me and it makes me uncomfortable.
So I'll just avoid the problem.
I hope a scrawny kit. Yeah, yeah, yeah, whatever.
I can sell the squirrel.
Eight gold?
This is not bad price.
Sir, take my animals.
How about the vicious death weed and shit?
Maybe I can use that for something.
This has no value.
What about... No, this is worthless.
Whoa!
These are worth a lot! Let's test something.
44 silver here.
I suspect Hanno will pay more for it.
Die trader, right?
My dear, what you're wearing
is much too drab.
You absolutely must take a lesson in dying
your tire to tire.
Maybe.
Would you like some...
Hey, you pay less?
Well, okay then.
I was wrong in my assumption there.
How much do you pay?
Oh wait, you can't.
Dolgen.
42.
Man, Ralph is the real one here.
He likes this.
That's for you, buddy.
I was about to say bro and buddy at the same time,
so it became bruddy.
Bombs are not worth that much.
Is this per or in total?
Let's see.
Wait.
23 silver.
Okay, it's in total.
I see.
Gotcha.
Increases defense by 8.
Isn't that kind of crazy?
Like, I have a total of 4 right now
with all of my gear.
And that will just straight up give me 8?
Oh my god, there's a lot of stuff there.
I kind of want that.
Let me go grab it.
No.
Oh, did I get it?
Or did this motherfucking demon eye
just take it from me?
I bring you the richest colors
in exchange for your riches.
Hmm.
Brown dye and silver dye.
I don't want that.
I don't want that, dude.
I want to go murder things and mine.
Gotta take a swig before we go mining, though.
That's what I'm talking about.
Okay. See, this seemed cool.
This little spot here, this can be
like a little outpost
before we go further, you know?
Let's see what I can find down here.
Actually, wait, wait, wait,
we're gonna go back up real quick.
I want to see if I can't make a better
pig axe.
How do I jump off properly?
This pig axe sucks.
Uh, let's see.
We need bars for that.
I put them here.
Tin bars and
gold bars.
Didn't I get some tungsten stuff?
Somewhere I did.
But I'm taking the bars anyway.
Iron ore, thanks.
What about in here?
What is happening with these
fallen stars?
Why are there so many of them?
What is a mushroom torch?
I have so many questions
in this game.
Okay, you can pick them up like that.
Now we have that confirmed
for real.
Come on!
Okay, I'm gonna take all these.
Maybe I should explore the desert.
Man, what's with all the falling stars?
They're everywhere.
Where?
I mean, I can keep collecting these
if there's no end to this.
Gimme!
There we go.
Firefly!
Maybe I can use that for something cool.
Okay.
Let's see.
I can make tin.
But where's the pickaxe?
Let me smell some shit.
Lead bar, sure.
Make all of those.
Let's make a bunch of these.
And...
It's kinda crazy that I can just do this.
How do I use my mana though?
That's another question I have.
Torch.
Silver.
Yeah, I need to go mine some shit.
I don't think I have what it takes.
Also, my inventory is kinda shit again.
Why am I so bad at managing
inventories in video games?
It's always an issue with me.
Let's sort first.
Like that.
Random ass shit.
Let's just put all this in here.
This one I want to keep, actually.
This one I want to bring as well.
All this can go in.
All that.
This will bring clay blocks
and cobwebs. Don't need it.
Neither do I need that.
The bars go in here.
All the ore.
See, that's what I'm talking about.
And now, we're ready.
Oh, let me just grab these.
I mean, why not, right?
No!
They have disappeared.
They is upon us.
What is this background?
Planked wall.
Oh.
Oh, isn't that interesting.
What if I use it like...
Oh, this is actually pretty nice.
I'm liking the auto thing here.
What's that?
What's this?
Platinum!
Tell me I can make tools out of that.
Let's keep going down.
Down!
We got water here.
In fact, maybe I can fish here.
What's that?
It's shiny.
I want to use this now.
Let's put it...
Also, wait a minute.
Wasn't there a...
Can I have multiple bars?
I wonder.
Block swap on.
Hold on.
Settings.
Cycle.
Left and right.
Let's just try and bind this to something.
I'm sure.
Where is this?
Oh, okay.
It's just going through. I see.
Okay. All right, all right, all right.
Let's see here.
It's working.
We're fishing.
Hey!
Maybe we need bait.
Oh, no. Did I leave the bait at home?
God damn it.
Let's actually try. Let's just see and wait.
Maybe something will happen.
Just like Minecraft.
Fitting a...
Oh, I can walk while I do this. Nice.
Come on, fishies.
Bite on it.
What if I walk far away?
Whatever.
I think I need some bait.
What's that? Wait, this is nuts.
What is that?
Tongsten!
That's what that looks like!
That's what I need!
Fuck yeah!
That's just stone.
Okay, man!
Lovely!
Let's keep going.
I want more.
I want to make tungsten everything.
Tungsten tables, tungsten chairs,
and tungsten cabalabras,
or candelabras.
Give me that. Sure. What's this?
Mud block.
Sure.
Mud is useful, right?
What do I see?
Oh, wait, I see something up there.
I see things!
In my peripheral vision.
Things that need to come home with me.
Get rid of that shit.
Okay, now we need to make something smart happen.
Platform.
What?
Look at this.
There we go. That's how you do it.
Oh, this is lead.
Okay, okay.
Grab it.
Okay, good. Let's keep going.
I want to find a cave.
Actually, there was a nice cave in that one spot
with the trees that I discovered earlier.
I should probably go back there.
Dude, why is mining so much fun in video games?
I don't understand this.
You're hitting a block. It's like the funniest
profession in video games.
And it's probably the worst profession in real life.
Why is it so satisfying?
What's that?
Oh, I need to make a platform.
Oh, no, what's that?
There's something in the water.
Oh, it's a centipede.
Bro, that thing just went...
Yo, come here.
Fuck you.
Dude, that was creepy.
Well, okay then.
I don't want to go for a swim anyway.
I just want to do this.
Yes, platinum.
Give me all of that.
I wonder if there's alchemy that I can actually craft my own shit.
I want to make potions.
I want to make gear.
I want to make food.
I want to make all the things.
Stone.
Wait, dirt.
Yeah, just keep going through the dirt.
That's fine.
It's actually pretty nice to have this automatic selection on the tiles.
So you don't have to manually click on the tiny, tiny tiles.
Okay, here's what I'm going to do.
Oh, whoa, whoa.
Ah, I see something up there.
Look at that, look at that.
On my peripheral vision, I see it.
This is... hold on, it is...
Fuck, what's the name? It's not platinum, it's tungsten.
Yes.
Steel trap.
What is that?
Oh, it's tin.
What's up, tin?
Just grab it all, I guess.
And then we also have more tungsten.
This is great.
And I can make platforms if I had wood, but I don't have wood, so rip.
Make a little platform I can stand on.
Like that.
Dude, I'm getting so much stuff.
This feels amazing.
Hell yeah.
Okay.
Man, we got a bunch of shit. I'm going back.
I want a craft. I want to make bars.
Do this.
Hey, I'm taking that.
Feels good to be home. What's up, people?
Joe, how you doing? Dolgen?
Trying to get past that crimp stone, eh?
Why not introduce it to one of these explosives?
Happiness.
Ah, no one around.
I can test new bombs without creating a graveyard.
You said that already.
So here we go.
Oh, we're making bars.
Make it all. That's all?
Wow, that's not a lot. I thought we could make way more out of that.
Lead bar. Let's make lead.
Oh, we can only make two.
Tin bar.
Let's make all the four.
And then we have platinum. This one we got a lot of.
Five, I say.
Seven.
Not bad.
Okay.
Let's see here.
Platinum bow. It is better.
Why can't I make a goddamn pickaxe?
What is happening?
What am I missing?
Also, why can't I make...
Oh, tungsten.
Huh.
Hold on a second. I want to try something again.
Hey, Joe!
What is this?
Crafting.
So, I'm in crafting mode.
It seems.
Oh, play some... wait!
Play some material here.
Oh!
Showing recipes that use platinum bar.
Oh, I get it!
Fucking hell.
Ah, requires ten.
I see...
Flinkstaff.
Okay.
And hell missing shit.
Watch.
Tells the time.
I guess that is useful.
Because it's hard to know what time it is.
You can't look up in the sky and look at the sun, right?
Platinum chandelier!
Let's not be extravagant here.
We need to be useful in our use of materials.
Let's make a throne.
Let's do it.
20 silk and 30 platinum bars.
Oh!
Magic mirror gazing the mirror to return home.
Now that looks very useful.
Doesn't it?
My goodness.
Okay, so we need ten.
Bro, I'll be back.
To check out more recipes and all the other things.
I know where to go.
Yank!
Scratch!
Thanks.
Also, is that a bug?
No.
We've got a bird.
It's just a bird. I love it.
Doot, doot.
Doot, doot, doot, doot, doot, doot, doot, doot.
Hey, come here, bird.
Explosions in a little firework.
It was to celebrate the arrival of the bird.
It was not to try and kill the bird.
Just making that clear here.
What is that?
Wait, what?
Oh, wait a minute.
Put this back. I get it now.
Oh, I placed it.
Thanks.
Now, it wasn't here. It was here.
This is my spot.
And down we go.
Okay, what do we got?
This is where I went.
Wait, am I seeing?
Oh! Oh!
I see it.
I can't wait to upgrade this shitty pickaxe.
I can't wait to see the speed.
Give me platinum.
I need... I require all the metals.
Yeah.
I need all the metals in the world.
For my experiments.
Back at home.
Yeah.
Very good.
Materials for me.
Give me a hair.
What's that?
Mud blocks.
We don't want to go this way. We want to go further down.
And also, there's something in here it seems.
I think that's...
Tin? Or lead?
What is it? Lead.
Okay.
Nice. Lead there will be loot.
And then we have more tungsten.
I mean tungsten.
Who needs tungsten nowadays when you have platinum?
Huh?
I shall have all the platinum.
But I'm just taking this, you know?
In case there's other things to make out of tungsten.
It's just common sense to grab.
Oh, there's things in there.
This is a cool cave.
I like this song.
Swiftness potion!
World of Warcraft memories.
Where is it?
There it is. 25% in 8 minutes.
Yo, these potions don't fuck around.
Let's drink it.
Oh, nice.
We shall be mining twice as fast now.
Actually, that doesn't make any sense.
We shall be traversing the mines twice as fast now.
And when I say twice as fast, I mean 20% faster.
Just to clarify here.
What's that? Cave bat!
Don't you...
It's an enemy.
I'm dying.
I'm dead.
Drop down!
Ooh, that was close.
Holy cannoli.
Brother!
That was scary.
I am not engaging in any combat activities in the next while.
We shall relax and stay passive.
We see more down here.
Tim.
What's up, Tim?
I liked him.
The good guy.
Okay, so here we start to...
Ooh, we need more wood.
Wait, I can make it.
There.
Eat that.
We drop down.
And then it's like...
Is it here?
Yep.
And then here.
Ooh, ooh, ooh.
What is that?
It's mother slime.
Okay, okay.
Can I shoot down?
Oh, I sure can.
Hey!
Hands up!
What is that?
It's a...
Cocheneal beetle.
There it is.
Beautiful.
How am I doing this?
In a smart way.
There probably is no smart way here to do that.
I see more tongues than there that I want.
But I need to eat.
I say just go.
Red husk.
Did I just take damage?
I just took damage from something.
Oh, the platform is incredible.
You can just do this.
Loving the platform.
Okay, now we're going to require all of this.
We've got slimes incoming!
Man, I wonder how I can make magic happen.
I want to use my mana.
Somehow.
Oh, yeah.
You know what tungsten means in Danish if you directly translate it?
tungsten means heavy stone.
tungsten.
Isn't that a fun fact?
I think it's funny.
I can't stop laughing.
This is a little bit troublesome.
Why is there a torch over there?
Wait, I've been here.
I get it.
I was here earlier.
Get away from me.
Oh, shit, I'm dying!
Funny games are over.
We've got to make a double wall here.
Oh, god.
Can I torch it?
There we go.
I don't even trust the double. We need a triple.
The triple floor.
The most feared of all the floors in the land.
Get away from me.
Triple floor!
No.
Eat.
I can't eat yet.
What's this?
Feral bite, increased damage, decreased life regen.
Causes status effects.
That's not good.
Look at the water flowing down.
That's so awesome.
At least the water physics here makes sense
compared to Minecraft.
I had such trouble understanding that system, bro.
The water in that game is
somethings to behold.
Okay.
Oh wait, we're in this fucked up region now.
Yeah, that ain't good.
I want to go up here, actually. Red slime.
Don't you ear me.
Okay, see, here I cannot use the platform strategy.
So, I should make
rope coil.
Look at this.
Hey.
That's a worm.
I shall take you.
Oh, switch.
No, you switch to the weapon, you idiot.
God damn.
Okay, I gotta go back and grab those items.
Actually, it's just gold, isn't it?
Fireworks.
Yeah, dude, imagine if we lost
items.
Dying.
That would have been rough.
No, the good arrows are gone.
That's okay.
Okay.
They have 90 HP still.
Okay, never mind.
I was about to say they had more HP, but they don't, actually.
I'm gonna go out on a limb here and say that
their HP numbers depend on far away from spawn you are.
That's the only thing that makes sense to me right now.
Or it's based on some sort of a
progression thing where
let's say I make a platinum sword.
You know, the game is like, okay, he's made it quite far.
This dude right here.
We gotta throw him some monsters that deal some damage.
Something like that.
Also, we're going out doing the night.
It's kind of dangerous.
But that's my middle name.
I don't care.
When I have this weapon right here,
nothing can hurt me.
Except that guy that killed me last time.
What is this?
It's just the OO.
Tell me they're not gonna fall down here into this place.
That would make me immensely unhappy.
See, do I take damage falling on these
stalax things? No, I don't.
I just want to see if there's any loot down here.
Oh no, they're coming down here now.
I wonder if monsters fight each other.
You know, do the slimes engage with these face monsters?
They have 140 HP.
I love this song.
It fills me with joy.
My joy is full.
What's that?
Oh, we've got something special.
Purple glowy thing.
Amethyst.
Fuck yeah.
Okay, activate this.
Makes it quicker.
Give me, give me, give me.
Noice.
And...
Tungsten. Where's my platinum?
I need a bit more platinum to make my platinum pickaxe.
Because who do you think I am? Someone who wants to make a tungsten pickaxe?
No way, sir.
That's below me.
I go only for platinum.
Also, these guys are about to die.
I've had enough of their ugly faces.
Come here.
Hey, sir!
Get cheesed.
What are you gonna do about it?
Oh, I get it now. You see?
It's not actually enough, this weapon, to knock them back.
So you need a weapon with bigger knockback against these monsters.
To keep them at bay while standing still.
Slime is falling from the sky.
What?
What the fuck are you on about?
Oh, come on.
You!
Piece of shit.
There it is.
You are gone, sir.
Do we have anything interesting in here?
Let's take a quick peek.
I should really explore near the edges here a lot.
Like, walking like this, you know?
Just to see, is there anything up there?
Doesn't look like there is.
I'm gonna keep dropping here.
Is this where I lost my money?
Mother...
Mother slime, you're about to die, mother.
Can you jump up here?
Oh, you can.
Oh, I'm gonna make a platform.
This is the genius method.
Mentored in 84.
By the supreme people.
In the mountains!
Oh, I don't have special arrows, though.
That's okay.
Nice.
Whoa, it spawned a little slime!
Oh, God.
Oh, God!
Okay, we're fine.
Good to know, though.
Oh, I can't drink it. I have to wait a bit.
I think I want to eat this. This is better.
In the long run, isn't it?
Money there.
I wonder if that money disappears after a while.
120 HP.
I don't want to risk it. Just kill him from here.
Oh! You motherfucker!
No!
He threw something at me.
Put me in a glass coffin?
Well, okay.
I need to make more of those kick-out arrows.
Oh, I didn't even see you there.
It's raining slimes!
They weren't kidding.
Why is it raining slimes?
What's happening?
This is weird!
What the fuck?
Ooh, that's nice.
My goodness!
Come here.
Stupid slimes.
What did I get?
I have defeated the 50th blue slime.
Feels good, man.
What's this?
Blue slime banner.
I don't just...
Oh, I can turn it off and on. That's awesome.
I don't think I can...
Stop this from happening. I just need to move on.
The slimes keep falling.
There's no reason to stay here.
Jump.
Just leave.
We gotta get out of here.
This game is so weird.
But in a fun way.
Very unexpected things happen here.
I also want to try and just walk left.
Like forever. Just avoid enemies, just go.
You know?
To the end of the earth.
I wonder if I'll loop back and come around on the right side after enough time.
How they gonna handle that? It's not a flat earth situation, is it?
You fall off the earth at the end.
Okay, let me go try here now.
Let's do this.
Did we see any oars?
This is what we were before. I want to pick up my money.
That's the important thing here.
There.
Thank you.
And then over here.
Oh yeah, look at all that money.
Nice.
Thank you.
They're so quick.
You always get hit by it.
I can kill these things.
I don't even care.
Maybe I care a bit.
Minimal amount of carrying.
This guy also has a helmet.
Oh my god.
Hey.
Oh, you know what I'm gonna do.
I'm gonna consume my...
Iron skin potion.
Drop.
Now I have 12 defense.
Let's see how much damage I take.
Hit me.
I still take a lot of damage.
I gotta be careful.
But it's definitely improved, I think.
Wait, what's...
What's happening?
I can't go right. I mean left.
Oh, now I can.
That was weird just now.
There's a chest down there that I really want.
I need to wait to heal.
There.
Do I have any actual foods?
15 life.
Oh man.
Oh, what is this?
Is that platinum?
Tell me that's platinum.
Yes.
That's what I was looking for.
Slamming coming.
I say no to that. I reject. I reject.
What are you gonna do now, huh?
A piece of dirt.
And you're stopping your tracks.
Very nice.
See, that's awesome.
How much can I make out of this now, I wonder?
Shit, I don't know where it is.
I just know I need a lot of it.
I don't think I have enough to make three bars.
It's all insane.
There's a chest down there.
That's intriguing.
Come here.
I know you want to come here.
Hey.
There it is.
Archery potion.
Bro, hell yeah.
Healing potion.
Flare.
Flare gun.
Blink root.
Oh my god, I have so many things.
Oh no.
Get away from me.
Major improvements to all stats.
Well done with ketchup.
That's not good.
Don't do that.
Wait, worm?
Bait power.
Let's put some stuff in here that I don't need.
What do I not need?
I don't know.
Eat this.
There we go.
That's one more spot.
Let's put the gel in here.
We're going to pick up lots of gel.
There's no reason to throw that away.
Put this in there.
And this one.
And that one.
All this.
The blue slime banner.
How do I freaking use this?
Is it an item I can equip?
Wait, where did it go?
I swear to god.
Where did I just put it?
I am blind as fuck, dude.
Oh, it's in the chest, isn't it?
I'm an idiot.
Okay, it doesn't work like that.
How do I place the banner?
I want to have increased damage against slimes.
All right, fine. Maybe I just throw it.
I don't know, man.
Plank wall? I don't need that.
I don't need that either.
Or this.
He's going to go in here as well.
They are not essential right now.
Okay.
I do want flare and flare gun and dynamite.
Your flare gun?
Yo, that's awesome!
Fuck yeah!
Do we still have a potion?
In case we need to get home.
We do.
Lovely.
Cool.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh!
We're fine.
The blue jellyfish.
Looks like it has electricity on it.
Oh, look at this!
It's jellyfish country.
I'm scared.
Why am I scared?
It's beautiful though.
The efficient way to get...
What is sport bat?
Get out of here.
Stupid sport bat.
Now, can I make...
A sticky bomb...
Web rope.
Make a lot of that.
Yes.
Question. Can I...
Oh no!
It couldn't...
Brother!
I can't control my shit.
Oh no, I can't see anything.
Kill them all!
Oh, I'm actually going to die here.
Holy shit.
I imagined the shelter!
I can't!
Okay.
That works.
Okay, chill out for a moment.
I don't trust this.
Okay.
What's that?
Why is it copper coin?
Why is it doing that?
Okay, I got to eat something.
I want that steak.
Ten seconds, though.
I think the iron skin has saved our ass here.
It probably would have died if not for that.
Spore skeletons.
Look at that. There's a heart over there.
I want to try and grab that.
Am I restoring? I am. Good.
Okay, let's go fuck this guy up.
Man, doing this like...
does a lot of damage.
I am scared.
Glowing mushroom, all kinds of crap.
Live crystal!
Heartbreaker.
Wait, I got an extra? Or what? No, I still have 100 HP.
Never mind.
I have to remember, these spawn the smaller slimes.
That's just like Minecraft.
Glowing mushroom.
Oh, that's big!
Fuck yeah, dude!
Love it!
I need more of that.
There's another one!
Yeah, dude!
Oh!
This is big!
I need this now.
Look at that!
What's that down there? There's an axe?
Excuse me, sir.
Oh, yeah.
I love the boat!
It's my favorite weapon.
100%.
Beautiful!
Let's see what we got.
No, it's the statue of an axe!
That's such a troll!
Hey!
There we go.
That's the healing potions.
Dude, this is a loot pinata!
I love it.
I need to plant forms.
That works.
Not quite the most optimal or beautiful solution there, but...
It is what it is!
Bombs?
Should I be bombing shit?
Hold on a sec here.
Oh! Oh no!
Centipede!
Did it die?
I think it's in the water.
Dude, it helps so much having that extra HP.
It's a big deal.
Bro, this is great.
How much damage does it do?
Hold on, I'm gonna try this here.
Gotcha.
Hey, buddies!
Look what I've got.
Oh, that's...
Whoa!
Yo, I love the bomb!
The bomb is great!
That's like a sick amount of damage.
And the best thing is I have a shit ton of bombs at home.
I'm bringing that next time for a show.
Why does it look like that guy has an alien rifle on him?
Hey, come here.
You there!
What is with these statues?
Why are there statues of everything in this game?
This world is filled with them for some reason.
Okay.
Where do I want to go?
Maybe it's time to head home.
No, it's not time to head home.
We keep going.
I need to find more of those hearts.
That's such a crazy upgrade.
And I'm not even sure I have enough platinum to do what I want to do.
And boy, do I have plans to do what I want to do.
You know what, I need some...
What's that?
Rally?
I can't tell what an icon is.
Let's see.
Is that a yo-yo?
Blue Fairy?
Can I catch you?
It's a yo-yo.
Oh!
Come at me.
Where is it?
Here, come check us.
There we go.
I hate those enemies.
They make me very uneasy.
Okay, go here now.
Look for items.
Oh, it's scouting for me!
Look!
I think it's telling me where there's an ore.
I'm coming, Fairy!
Fairy, I'm coming!
Wait, wait, wait, I'm gonna...
Man, I need a better pickaxe. This shit is slow!
Holy shit, this stone right here is...
Plentiful.
What is that down there?
It's totally guiding me towards something.
I'm gonna trust 100% into this fairy right here.
Now there's a piece of ore right there that's very intriguing to me.
What is that?
Blinkroot.
I had more of those.
Blinkroot seeds.
Whoa, wait!
Can I... farming?
Can I do farming?
I need to make farming happen.
I need to plant things.
I hope that's what that means.
I really hope so.
Okay, we made it into another cave system.
And it's time to utilize this shit ton of this rope we have.
And this is awesome.
What's that?
I think the fairy led me to a heart.
But then it disappeared.
Throwaway cobweb.
Away you go.
Where is it?
There.
Fuck yeah.
God, that feels good.
We're so strong!
Nothing can stop me now.
Wait, I can craft?
Explosive body!
You gotta be shitting me.
No way.
What do you mean?
Hold on now.
Give me enemy.
Oh god, what was that?
Oh!
Perfect.
Hey!
Do I remote detonate it?
No.
I can shoot it with a bow probably when it gets close.
What?
Oliver's top knot was carved off by boulder.
Jesus.
Wait, a hoplite?
Isn't that a Greek warrior or something?
Not Greek, but...
What's the name?
You know, fucking...
movie star guy.
Brad Pitt, dude.
In that movie.
Hoplite?
No, hoplite is definitely...
Is it Roman or Greek?
I don't fucking know.
It's one of them.
Listen to the birdsong.
Daybloom.
Bro, my inventory is...
terrible. I need to go back
and take care of that before I venture back in there.
That's just horrendous.
Also...
How do I move this...
How do I move this map?
Spawn.
Yo, this map is actually
insanely useful.
I should start using this map.
I mean, it's not like I'm lost yet.
I've gotten pretty good practice at navigating
through rain world.
I had my fair share of times
when I was lost in that game.
I don't even need the map right now. This is so easy
without the map, but I probably will need it
at some point.
Ralph?
Let me sell you a bunch of shit.
Here's the thing. I don't want to sell
everything because
it can be used, no?
The statue thingy is...
Wait.
Let me hop up here.
We need more chests.
We need chests.
We don't have enough.
Can I make those?
Dude, I can make all kinds of things now.
I can make a pocket!
Can be used to scoop up a small amount of liquid.
I love scooping!
Mushroom chair.
Here.
Let's make one chest.
Okay, there.
Yeah, sure. Put this in.
Stone blocks can stay because
I'm probably going to get more of that.
It's time...
It's time to smelt.
Platinum.
Yeah!
Make all the lead.
Oh, that's all I got.
And make
all the tin.
Wait, um...
Sword inventory?
And then we... let me actually test this.
Quick stack to nearby chests.
Yo, that's a great feature!
Holy shit!
That right there
is fucking incredible.
Can I just say that?
You make chests for certain things.
You go out and explore.
Then you come home
and you just click that button
and everything goes in.
It goes straight in.
That's amazing.
Incredible.
Stack to all the chests
actually stack like this.
Okay.
Now.
Give me all the bars.
Um, yeah, that's good.
Let's see here. That, that and...
Give me that, give me that.
Give me that.
Sure, give me that as well.
And then do that.
Now, will this stack
even more?
I love stacking.
Let's just make what we can make here.
So now I had it here.
Now I put it there.
If I now sort, will it automatically
sort into the already stacked?
It will. And I love that.
I love that.
The reason I'm so happy about all this
is because I suck at inventory management
and if this can help me
then I'm all for it.
You know?
Okay. Now that we have all the
ingredients
Let's see what we can make, huh?
What can we make?
Wait.
Joe!
Tell me.
What do I need?
Platinum bar?
And wood.
Oh, I don't have wood.
Oh, is that it?
Hell yeah, dude.
I can have that.
Somewhere I must have wood.
Maybe not, actually.
Let's go chop some wood.
I will take you with me because
I want to make bunny explosives.
Thanks.
That's so insane that you can make
bunny explosives.
Give me that.
Let's see.
Tell me we can make it now.
What just happened over there?
The slime just murdered a bird, I think.
Yes!
Very fast speed.
59% pig-axe power.
50%.
35. What is mine at?
35.
Okay, this is going to be
a significant improvement,
me thinks.
Yeah!
Ralph, you beautiful bastard.
Look at this.
I have gotten a platinum pig-axe.
What else can I make?
I can make an amethyst gem-corn
for some reason.
Dude, the mine carts?
I want to make that so bad.
There's so many things I want to make.
Wait.
Why would I make a lead anvil?
Wait, is that the same thing I already have?
I wonder if that's going to produce
different things.
Trapdoor!
They exist?
Any iron bar
and any wood.
Cool.
All right.
Awesome.
Hold on, I need to take a look in here, actually.
Let's take a look here.
Merchant.
Merchant acts
as a simple general store of sorts
providing useful starter tools
and supplies needed for exploration.
What does this mean?
Demolitionist.
Tread carefully around this dwarf.
Oh, it's a dwarf.
A demolitionist is an explosive fanatic
and sells dangerous things that go boom.
Wait.
Wait a minute.
Is this saying that I need to build him a house underground?
And he's more happy there?
Exotic scimitar?
Is that if I kill him?
Two stars.
Accentric and rather snobby to a fault.
The dye trader has expensive tastes.
He is passionate about the materials used
in the dyes he sells.
Not the typical garden variety, bunny.
This one has been tampered with
and has an explosive temper as a result.
What is the deal with these?
Oh, I wonder if I
get more information about them.
The more I slay.
Oh, they only appear during rain.
That makes sense, actually.
Can I...
Demon eye?
Oh, I get to see drops later on?
I love this!
I hate that.
I don't like this. I hate this.
Spiders, not my thing.
Giant Shelley.
Caverns.
Wait, what's the difference between that and underground?
A ghost.
Graveyard.
Right.
That makes a lot of sense.
The owl?
A large, wise predatory bird
which hunts nocturnally from the treetops.
Man, I wonder...
what this means.
It took at the best area 540 entries.
That's insanity.
Okay, well, well, well, well, well.
Alright.
Okay.
What else should I make here?
I think I'm gonna make some good old armor.
Huh?
I have a lot of tungsten.
Let's make the chainmail.
Replace the wooden shit.
Man.
How do I frickin...
I don't understand this.
Oh, wait.
I think I get it.
It's just gone.
So whenever I put a new one in, it's...
I think I understand.
So if I were to do...
Let's say...
I don't even know what to destroy.
Maybe an acorn.
Yeah, and it's just gone.
Fuck, yeah.
Finally, I figured that out.
Equip your first grappling hook.
See, that's what I want.
That sounds awesome.
Look, they go straight in.
It's a good feeling.
Ralph!
I will be upon a soon friend
to make your choices while you can.
Happiness.
Okay, whatever.
I think that's supposed to ask him
what he likes
so I can give him the best possible
treatment
in this local community.
Um...
I don't know about these statues, man.
I'll keep them for now.
Maybe I'll make a little statue
garden at some point.
Seems pretty cool
to do something like that.
Now, this right here
is kind of crap.
That shall be sold.
Hold on, can't be placed.
Maybe it needs to be
placed on a stick.
If you think about it, that makes sense, doesn't it?
Or like a pole.
Um...
Is there a question?
I can rename?
Michelinius.
So can I see that one?
Oh, that's so good.
I shall rename you.
Um, let's say
Ors
and
Doors.
Those are the two things
that go in here.
Ors and Doors.
Uh, the Annoying Copper Axe
shall be sold.
Uh, the statues
go in here
into Michelinius.
No, there we go.
Workbench is also Michelinius.
Let me actually sell a bit to you.
No, General Store.
This is a normal copper pickaxe.
It's not an annoying one.
Anyway, this is a demonic one.
I wonder if this is randomized.
Let's say I started a new game.
I wonder if I would have had this
in my inventory.
Or something else.
Minus one range on that, look.
Is that why it's demonic?
Sell that shit.
And I don't know
why he would buy something that's annoying,
but sure, take it. Man, these sell for a lot.
They sell for a lot.
Okay, let's see if we can go plant some shit.
How does this even work?
I think I need a hoe.
I need to till the earth.
Can I make something like that?
I haven't seen it yet, but let me talk to Joe.
He's just resting in his chair right now.
What's this?
That goes away.
Oh my, oh my, oh my.
Joe!
Tell me about...
What was I about to ask you?
Fuck, what was it?
Joe, tell me.
I wanted to make a hoe.
So how about I give you
some wood?
No.
How about I give you tin?
Can I make a tin hoe?
Pig eggs.
Hammer.
Topaz staff.
Uses mana.
I'm going to make a stopwatch.
Bro, these fucking things are annoying.
Get out of my sight.
I'm dealing with Joe.
Joe.
What were we?
What can I do with this, Joe?
I can make red die. Thanks, Joe.
Now, Joe, what can I do with an amethyst?
Purple... why would I do that?
Purple stained glass.
Green spark block.
Amethyst robe?
Maybe like a sorcerer style.
Amethyst staff and hook.
Grappling hook?
Wait.
Lightsaber?
Gem lock.
Hmm.
For capture the gem, it drops when you die?
Yo, hold on a second now.
Oh, I need 15.
Shit, I can't make it.
Hey, Joe.
What about the lead?
I can make all kinds of things with this, it seems.
Dude, there are items to craft in this game.
Holy crap, there's a lot.
A gate.
I want to make like a whole courtyard and stuff.
A palm wood clock?
Is that an owl right here?
Oh, yeah, it is. There's an owl right there.
I like the sound of that owl.
That's a nice sound.
Dude, what the fuck?
Dude, this never ends.
Barrel, carpentry rack!
Hold on a second now.
Rafting. I need chain.
Hold on, I can make that shit.
I can make a chain!
Can I not?
Chain!
Mushroom lantern.
Bro, the crafting is very advanced in this game.
That's insane.
Wait, what else did I need? Wood, right?
You know what? It's time to...
It's time to plant some trees!
Give me that.
What's that? There's some kind of mushroom over there.
What's that? It's an owl.
Did I have trees on me?
Probably not.
Michelinius.
Let's see here.
Acorn.
That's what I need for that, I believe.
Uh...
Yes, I catch you.
And then...
Let me put this here.
Yes!
We're making a forest.
Lots of trees. I wonder how this is gonna work.
Also, I may have to water them.
Probably with the bucket, right?
Fill it with water.
And then over here as well.
Dude, this is gonna be a dense-ass forest.
Now, what is this?
Leaf wand. Consumes wood places leaves.
Okay.
Then we had living wood wand.
I think it says zero.
I need some kind of ammo for that.
And I'm not sure how exactly that works.
Flowing mushroom.
It's a vibe.
But not one that I like.
Not in this...
Grasshoppers.
You shall be mine.
Oh, I guess the owl came with me too.
I don't wanna...
You know what? This owl right here.
You get to be right there.
Hang out there and make owl noises for me, please.
I wonder how long it takes for this to grow.
What is this thing right here?
Mushroom. Right.
Okay, I'm gonna grab some more wood here because I needed to construct things.
Dankeschön.
Thank you.
What's that?
Oh, it's just a reminder of the early game here.
Don't don't...
The early game didn't happen.
That was kind of a tough time there.
99 and 80, okay.
I don't think their health are increasing.
It's like hovering around the 90s and 80s, you know?
It's not significant enough to...
What was that?
A lemon!
Minor improvements to all stats.
Right.
Yeah, I should...
You know what? Sure, eat it.
I don't have much inventory anyway.
I can't wait to test this pickaxe.
In action, you know?
Look at the skills here.
Look at that!
Totally not getting carried by this insane weapon that I found.
Oh my god, it's so good.
Oh, thanks!
That thing just fell on my head.
Oh! Hold on, I'm not actually understanding...
What is the point of...
Whoa!
I can do things.
Alright, fine.
Please leave me alone.
I think I have enough wood anyway.
Then again...
Can you really ever have enough...
It's just like Minecraft.
You think you have enough and then you always end up needing more.
Also, is it just me or am I walking faster than normal?
I feel like I have more movement.
Ah, let's see here.
Now I can probably make something cool.
Here we go.
I see new things.
Galleous the Travelling Merchant has arrived!
So we have to make a table.
Table!
You get to be up here for now.
I wonder if I can put multiple in the same house.
Uh...
Wait...
Wait, oh, Travelling Merchant.
Maybe he's not here to stay.
Hey, meet me behind Joe's house in about three hours.
I think I have something you'll find very appealing.
Uh...
Okay.
Sounds good.
Kago Summon.
A brick layer.
Increases tile placement speed?
No way.
Yo, these are so expensive!
I don't have that much money!
Oh my god.
Sake.
Minor improvements to melee stats and lowered defense.
Drink too much of this and you become Karate Master.
Hmm...
And you also get drunk.
Blue Chicken.
Someone's a blue chicken.
Man, this is so expensive. I don't have all this money.
Oh, I shouldn't have died that much.
I had money at some point.
I was living a good life.
And now...
Not so much.
Hey, Hano.
You want to buy some stuff?
I kind of need money right now.
Blink root.
You know what?
Living would want.
Places living would.
You can have it, because I don't understand it yet.
Um...
The table, though, goes up here for now.
This is a temporary home for you.
We also need a chair.
Oh no, wait. You didn't need a home. Never mind.
You are a traveling man.
And you like to...
travel.
Uh...
Quick stack.
So let's put some stuff in here.
All this crap.
Man, we need more chests.
This is not enough.
I need to have a dedicated time
of just putting down a shit ton of chests.
Expanding my home.
I need a whole room
with chests.
And a big one at that.
And they need to be labeled.
Fallen... What's this? Abigal's flower.
Six summon damage.
Summon is a friendly ghost to fight for you.
It's hauntingly beautiful.
Huh!
I will try that.
We have this.
I don't want it in there.
We should have an organic chest.
Let's say...
Organics.
Okay, that's good for now.
Michelinius, organics, ores and doors.
We didn't have any doors, but we do have a...
You know what? I have to make a door.
You can't have a chest called that and not have a door, can you?
Except I don't have the materials.
So it's actually fine.
Now Galeus.
A thrift shop? No! I'm only selling the
highest quality items on the market.
Unfortunately, I don't have the money.
Can I offer you
some dirt in these trying times?
Or something?
Okay, let's just organic the fuck out of this up here.
Organics.
Let's remove anything that's not organic.
This is technically organic.
Glowstick?
I think it's organic.
This is not organic.
Bombs 30! I'm bringing those, man.
Next expedition, it's bombing time.
Oh, I do have a bunch of wood!
Holy shit, I forgot about that there.
Fireflies. Deathweed.
Now this right here, keen wooden hammer.
Is that what I started with?
Wait, I have an annoying tungsten hammer?
50% hammer power.
I think it's still better.
Wait a second here!
Do I get randomized items
when I craft them?
Holy shit.
That's a big discovery just now.
I just realized.
Okay.
So I should make multiple,
I guess, to see if I get better ones.
Wood helmet?
Fuck, now, you know what? I can sell things.
Worst case.
Acorns. Let's put anything organic in here.
So that, that, that.
Do-do-do-do-do.
Yeah.
No, this.
And what else do we have?
Flowing mushroom.
Okay.
That's a good start.
Gelanius.
We can put detonator in there.
And the statues.
Obelisks, we don't want to see those.
Never ever do we want to see those.
Now, dude, do you want to buy things?
That's the question.
Eleven copper? Hold on.
Will you buy it for more?
You won't.
But, because you have such extraordinary prices,
I feel like I should sell you all this crap.
You deserve to have it.
I...
I can just give him,
I can just give him two stones.
Sure, you can have him.
You can have this as well.
And shurikens.
Ten range of damage.
Very fast speed.
I should experiment with those.
Fifty silver.
Now, I don't know what that little
icon means underneath weak knockback.
I feel like...
there's something going on there.
But...
I need money.
I need that money.
I have only two of these right now.
And play... wait, this is an ammo.
Right, of course it is.
Yeah, yeah, it makes sense.
It makes a lot of sense.
Put that... actually, let me see here.
So this is a BRV.
Like that.
Now, here's what I want to do.
I want to make some proper goddamn meals.
In this game.
I want to cook.
Because I'm tired...
of constantly eating these mushrooms.
I need something real.
Something hearty and healthy.
Can I make an oven?
You know what?
Let's bring the stone...
that I have.
Do I not have... I have stone.
Hey, Joe!
My man!
Crafting?
What can I make?
Can I make an oven out of this stone?
Looks more like it's only...
Oh my god, there's so many items.
Plank wall!
Aha!
I do kind of like how this looks.
Maybe I will do that in the future.
Okay, furnace.
I already have that.
I can make statues with numbers.
What the heck, dude?
Can I see...
Ah, here we go.
Much better.
Arrows...
Tell me...
You know what?
Maybe campfire, actually.
So I had some animals, didn't I?
I'm gonna make bunny.
Let's see here.
Okay, that doesn't work.
Come back.
Maybe I have to be crafting menu while I'm here.
Next to the... what's that?
Why doesn't it say what it is?
Oh, the dirt bomb.
Oh!
You!
Get out of here.
Maybe I can use the furnace to cook food.
Now that I have my bunny on me, can I cook a bunny meal?
Life regen is increased when near a campfire.
Oh!
So it's like passively increased.
Or what?
You know what?
I probably need a bowl or a plate to make food.
Let's make a bowl.
Hey, Joe!
What can I do with a bowl, Joe?
Bowl...
Fruit salad!
Fuck yeah, man!
I need any fruit.
An apple a day keeps Dr. Bones away.
Sure.
So, I wanna make a plate now.
I don't have any apples, man.
Or any other fruit for that matter.
It's bowl time.
Where's the bowl?
I'm losing my...was it over here?
Plate!
That's what I needed.
Okay, Joe!
What can I do with a plate, Joe?
Plate...
Wait, really? Nothing?
Right, click to place item on plate.
I want Bonnie on plate.
Unless...
Unless I put it in the world first.
Bonnie on plate.
Nope.
Okay, he's back in my inventory.
I want Bonnie on plate!
Hey, Joe! What can I do with a lens?
Whoa!
Summons the twins.
Goggles?
Optic staff.
Deer thing!
What the fuck?
I can make another deer thing.
Archery potion that requires bottled water, day bloom and lens.
Okay.
Soul of light, the essence of light creatures.
What about glow stick, Joe?
A bouncy glow stick or a sticky glow stick?
Gel. Oh, I have a lot of that, actually.
Bouncy is only with pink.
Huh.
Alright.
Well, Joe, what about mud blocks?
Trees are growing!
Look! I saw it happen right before my eyes.
What about the star, Joe?
Super mana potion.
Oh my god, there are so many fucking items.
Enchanted boomerang.
Wouldn't boomerang.
Well, Joe, how do I make a boomerang?
Capricorn helmet.
Vanity item.
I don't know what vanity actually means.
Hold on, doesn't vanity mean only interested in external materialistic things and not of substance or something?
Something like that.
Star cannon!
But oh no, I need a mini shark to make that.
Joe, what's a mini shark?
Meteorite bar. Hold on.
This one can mine meteorite.
So whenever I find that, I guess I can do that.
Half shark, half gun. Completely awesome.
What is this game, dude?
Increases fishing power by 10.
See, that sounds like something I can get behind.
I like it.
Loose Dari block.
Star in a bottle.
Jester's arrow.
This is the one I already know how to make.
What is happening?
We have a demonic incursion, people!
Action stations! Action stations!
No!
Oh no!
Come on!
Red alert!
I need to heal.
Oh no. We've got the money, guys.
Hey!
I gotta protect my citizens!
I gotta protect myself first, though.
What is happening here?
Demons!
We're safe in here.
Let's try this.
Cool!
Hey, look, it's helping!
Lot zombie.
Nice! Fight for me!
Should I go outside?
Look, it's taking care of it!
Oh!
Wait, I can't drink yet.
Okay, he's gone, he's gone.
We've got zombies in the house!
Did that guy just sort of explode?
Dude, this is doing a ton of damage!
Oh my god, oh my god.
Come here!
How are they getting inside?
That's a star.
Oh, the doors are open.
Hey!
Wait, why don't they...
Close.
Oh, I have to right click. I see.
Okay, we're safe.
People, the situation is under control.
We have a ghost on our side and it's kicking ass.
Wait, they can open doors!
You're there.
Oliver has defeated the hundredth zombie!
Damn right.
Man, what is happening here? Why are they here?
Nice.
I mean, this is money in the bag, right?
Look at all this killing happening over here.
That's a crazy item.
Can I just keep using them?
Uses mana.
Okay, okay, okay.
Uh-oh, we've got people incoming.
Stars are falling.
It's raining blood.
I don't know how I'll feel about that.
What is that? It's a dribbler!
Good at basketball or something.
Bring potion.
Back into action.
Okay, we've got to protect here.
Gotta protect the citizens.
Hanno.
Oh, God.
Hanno, do you mind helping out just the tiny amount here?
Maybe?
Close that.
That thing is doing work.
Oh, God.
What's happening? What's happening?
Ralph, I'm sorry, I should not have opened that door.
I mean, this is money in the bag.
And we need money.
Oh, God, they're coming from the right side as well.
Close that door.
Oh, God, I protect you!
Okay, don't go near the door.
This is intense.
I got a drink potion.
There we go.
Back into action.
In fact, why don't I use arrows?
Seems like a great idea.
Dude, this ghost is doing work!
That's a little cute flower on its head too.
Oh, that money.
Close the door.
Looks like only some of the monsters are able to open the door.
We lost the trader, though.
The guy that I needed the money for in the first place.
Eh.
Oh, God.
Wait, they can't get down here, can they?
I have no more special arrows.
Dude, I'm swimming in money.
This is awesome.
Drink potion.
I just have to make it through the night, I guess.
Okay, it's going pretty well.
There's no way this keeps going, right?
It's gotta end.
Okay, let's go grab that star over here.
I need it to make better arrows.
Thank you very much.
For some reason, this door on the right is way more effective than the door on the left.
Get rid of that.
Nice.
What's happening over here?
I need to make more arrows.
I need to eat.
Wait, do my weapons crit sometimes?
There's a crit chance, no?
Sometimes it looks like I do way more damage.
Oh, look at this.
I can shoot down from here.
Stag them up!
Or stay nine, would say.
Line them up!
It's like a hellion running into a mineral field.
Blue flame.
That's what that is.
Uh oh, they're coming inside the house!
No other people under attack!
Drink potion.
Now I can drink.
Are we losing people?
Heno!
Bro, this is insanity.
But I'm farming all the gold.
This is actually no problem at all.
I do need some proper food.
I need to calm down a bit here.
This ghost right here is doing insane work.
It's time to blue flame the mineral line again.
Look at that! 42, that was a crit!
Wait, am I hitting the ghost?
Let's test something.
No, I'm not. Okay, good.
I'm not hitting the ghost.
Drink.
No, no more special arrows.
You, man, I'm already out.
That's insane.
Come on, Dawn.
When is Dawn here?
That's how we do it.
We're bringing the fight to them now.
Homestead is secure? Actually, it's not.
Nice! Bloodbath!
I did it!
Hell yeah.
We only lost one person.
And this demonic incursion...
Wait, did we lose more than one?
One, two, three.
Who's missing?
Ralph, Joe, Hano.
Wait, we had one more.
Who died?
Yeah.
Whoever was up here is dead now.
Fuck.
RIP.
Demon... there's a demon eye there.
That's not okay.
Dude, how long is this ghost lasting?
Someone's a friend that goes to fight for you.
Okay.
Well, this looks pretty insane to have with me.
If it's just always there.
Like, what the heck?
Okay.
Well, that's a good place to end it, I guess.
I need to go to sleep.
This is very late for me.
Unfortunately, there's no bed in the game, so...
And I hopefully am saving things automatically here.
Save and exit.
Dumb, dumb.
Dude, this game is pretty cool.
In fact, I spent way more time today than I initially planned to do.
This was supposed to be between three and four hours.
And look at us.
Five and a half hours.
Insane.
Hold on.
Check this out.
I want to show you something.
Get ready for the sick transitions.
You want to do that?
Let's bring it back.
And it goes away.
And it comes back.
Look at that.
Isn't that cool?
Something I said earlier.
Okay.
Do that.
And then...
Look at that.
Isn't that cool or what?
How are you doing, people?
Five yards centipede.
What's up, man?
Yeah, no spoilers.
Exactly.
Hold on.
Is there a way to actually have game volume while minimized?
Because I like the music here.
You know what?
I have a better idea.
We're going to do this.
Just a bit of that in the background there.
Some chill music there.
How's everybody, huh?
Let me see here.
Oh, wait.
Holy shit.
It's Santi.
Five euros.
Thank you, man.
I like your profile picture, by the way.
You changed it, didn't you?
Hello to the end of the stream.
You're cooking really good.
It's going to be one of the best playthrough starts I've seen.
Very excited for the series.
I don't know if you were here from the very beginning, though,
but the beginning was a disaster.
I got my ass kicked a lot in the beginning.
But it was fun.
And then we have Ludwig.
You've been a member for a month.
Nice.
Potat, you have now achieved a triangle status.
Much better than a straight line, you know?
So, welcome.
Again.
The Oolun.
Thanks for the two pounds, man.
Hi, chat.
Hi, Oolun.
I like your profile picture.
Reminds me of something from Hollow Knight.
Ludwig, you gifted five memberships to people.
Thank you, man.
Who are the lucky ones?
I do wonder if you're able to choose as well,
or if it's always random.
Let's see.
That's awesome.
Ludwig, thanks for hanging out and watching the stream
and gifting those subs.
That's awesome.
Elavi.
Thank you for the 10 euros, man.
Even in the darkest of times, let this knowledge
keep your spirits high.
This is just a kids' game.
How hard can it be?
All right, all right, all right.
You can laugh.
Okay, that was maybe...
Yeah.
That didn't age well, did it?
But you know what?
It's gotten better.
The beginning was rough, you know?
I feel like I got into a bad circle there at the beginning.
But it turned out all right.
Hello, future Oliver, whenever you read your donuts.
Hey, the Olon again.
With the extra one cent.
I love it.
Thanks, man.
And hey, past the Olon or the Ulun.
I don't actually know how to pronounce your name.
I'm sorry.
Sergei Svikolnikov.
I feel like I nailed that name first try.
Tell me if I did or not.
Thanks for the five euros.
Hey, Oliver, I recall you enjoyed Subnautica.
I would recommend you give a try to Grounded.
Very similar vibe in terms of exploration and progression.
So I actually did play a little bit of Grounded with one of my real life friends.
We played for like, I'm gonna say an hour.
But there were some spiders in that game that fucked me up.
I'm not sure I can play that game.
The spiders in that game are way too realistic and they mess with me.
That was rough.
Scary stuff.
But it seems like a solid game when I played it.
It seemed like a really fun game.
Yeah, it's a solid suggestion for sure.
Thanks Sergei.
The Ulun.
I enjoyed watching very long stream.
Yes, five and a half hours.
But I guess the first 30 minutes were the countdown and all that.
So five hours is indeed a long stream.
It's not something I'm used to doing.
I have done some in the past that were five hours.
Usually it's when I forget time, like today.
Ethan cubed.
Hey man.
Wait a minute.
Weren't you Ethan squared once?
And I promoted you to Ethan cubed.
Did you change your name?
Am I tripping right now?
Did I dream saying this or something?
Terraria is a great game. I hope you enjoy it.
It is.
So far it's fun.
I gotta say it's more fun than I was expecting.
I was a little bit, you know, in the beginning.
I mean, I did see some screenshots on Steam of the game.
And I looked at it.
I don't know man.
I don't know if this is gonna be for me.
But I gotta say it's super fun so far.
And I'm excited to play more of it.
So there it is.
It is a great game.
And Darth clone has joined the can.
You have achieved a straight line so far?
Welcome man.
Welcome to the can. That's really nice of you.
Welcome.
How's everybody else doing?
Did you enjoy the stream?
You called me Ethan squared once and I guess it stuck.
Wait, your name was always Ethan cubed?
No way.
All we're doing stream, the stream chat was covering the terrarium messages.
Oh, okay, okay.
Thanks for pointing that out debonair puma.
I'm gonna check up on that for next time.
Also, I kind of forgot.
I needed to check in with you after 30 minutes.
Regarding the audio, I hope it was fine during the game.
I completely forgot about that.
I'm sorry.
I was totally into the game.
I got sucked in, man.
Yashir Russel or Russell.
Thanks for showing it two days before we started because of that I finally caught one.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, I'm sorry. I don't do that as much.
It's simply because I have such a tight schedule
that I'm not really sure when I'm able to stream.
So it's something that I always decide on the day usually.
So within like 12 hours.
But yes, I will try to put them in advance as far as I can.
But it's just really difficult to fit it in.
Hey, Doc Hatter. Bye-bye, Oliver.
I don't know if this request got lost in the sea of others last time,
but if you enjoy inscription when you give that a go,
I'd like to also recommend
Hieronymus Bosch's Brutal Orchestra.
Hold on.
Hieronymus Bosch.
Isn't that also a guy from a TV show called Bosch?
It's a cool show, by the way.
I don't know if it's related at all.
But that sounds awesome.
Hold on, let me actually write that down.
I'm just gonna add it to my list.
I don't know if you've seen it,
but I put the list in my Discord of all the games that I have
planned to play.
It's long at this point.
Hieronymus...
Bosch.
Brutal Orchestra.
Okay, thanks, man.
The audio's been alright, I feel?
Okay, good. That's awesome.
It would have been so bad if I had gone for five hours
and the game was too loud or something, you know?
Audio was near perfect.
Oh, I'm so happy, guys.
Great.
This game really sucks you in.
It does!
I was not expecting that.
Every single Terraria player goes from
this game looks meh
to this is fun, actually,
to where all those hours of my life go.
Yeah.
Guilty of that one, too.
Audio was great, nice.
We need more jungle, I'm afraid.
Hey, Oliver, I haven't been here since Minecraft
because I only watch you play games I've played
to avoid spoilers.
Yeah, you should definitely, yeah.
Don't worry, it's all fine.
You should definitely play these games first.
They're awesome.
Honestly, all of the games I've played on the channel
so far have been awesome.
How's work been?
Eh.
A lot of work and...
Yeah, I don't know.
It's decent, I would say.
It's not fantastic and it's not terrible.
It's like in between.
Actual responsibilities.
Great stream.
Rough start, but I was expected with expert.
Yeah.
In the beginning I really
considered starting again
on a different difficulty.
I felt like I may have gone a little too crazy.
Picking expert, but now it's fitting.
It's fine now, yeah.
The eulon.
Thanks again for the pound, man.
Toasty inspiration.
Man, I remember you from the early days.
You've been here for so long.
Thanks for just sticking around.
Thanks for the 50 Kroners.
Be sure to ask the guide about everything.
Also great stream.
Yeah, Joe is my number two.
He's my main man
when it comes to figuring things out in this game so far.
Steve!
Thanks for the $3.
I'm glad you enjoyed the stream.
I'm sorry, I can't get to all of your messages, guys.
There's a lot of people watching right now.
There's 360 people watching.
So, I really can't get to all of your messages.
I'm so sorry.
You should play 4D Gold
made by Indie Dev Code Parade.
It's a new game, fairly short, but really mind-bending.
Hold on, I'm gonna write that.
I'm just adding all of these to the list.
By the way, you can see the list on Discord.
I don't know if any one of you here has not joined the Discord yet,
but it's a great community in there.
You should totally join.
It's awesome.
4D Gold...
Code Parade.
Okay.
I shall check it out, sir.
Well, I'm awake.
What did I miss?
Welcome, Omega Cannon.
You arrived just at the end.
I'm sorry.
You have perfect or worse timing, depending on how you look at it.
Actually, Expert is the regular mode.
Wait, really?
Are you sure about that?
Because the other mode did say the standard for Terraria or something.
Yeah, I picked Expert because it said that there would be better loot.
And I like that.
I like the sound of that.
It was a very good thing you started with Expert,
because without Expert, there's a lot of cool things you can get.
Yeah, exactly.
That's what I thought as well, shade 6877.
We peaked with 500, really?
There were 500 people watching.
That's insane.
I think that's the highest I've ever had it.
That's unreal.
Rip Maxwell.
Yeah.
But you know what?
He couldn't even defend himself in a fight.
I feel like Joe is superior to Maxwell.
Golf, not gold.
Oh, okay.
Thanks.
40 gold.
I was thinking to myself, 40 gold.
40 golf.
Okay.
Thanks.
Made a typo.
Guys, where in the Discord is the list?
Oh, I think someone posted it somewhere.
Maybe in the games channel?
At least people told me that we're going to post it there.
There were like 500 people watching.
That's insane, man.
Ori and the Blind Forest is also a great game that you should play.
Definitely among my favorite games.
The Lord Eternal is actually already on my list.
And they're making a second one, I believe.
Or maybe that's already out.
I'm not sure, but people have been praising that one, too.
Yeah, I've definitely heard about it.
I'd like to tell you about a game called Vintage Story.
Well, say no more, fam, it goes on the list.
I'm not going to guarantee that I play all the games on the list,
but the way this works is I just take all the suggestions from you guys
and, of course, the games that I've been eyeing myself,
put them all on a list.
And then when it's time to play a new game,
I just sort of choose whatever sounds good at the time, you know?
Vintage...
Vintage what did you say?
Vintage Story, okay.
Got it.
Next Terraria stream when? Oh, I'm not sure yet.
Actually, tomorrow is still Easter, isn't it?
I think tomorrow is still a holiday.
Maybe tomorrow, if not, definitely within the next couple of days.
Oh, the second Ori has been out for years now.
Oh, shit, okay, yeah.
Damn, yeah, I'm a little bit behind here.
Anti-Chamber, yeah, I've heard about that.
And I've only heard about it because Day 9 has played it once
and I watched, like, five minutes of it and it looked cool.
I've played some of Factorio already, Shadow Mallard.
Hey, Barry, welcome to the Potato.
You are now in my pantry and you shall be there
until you get consumed one day.
People must be so confused.
I don't even know what that means myself,
but it sounds good to say.
Yeah, Factorio is dangerous.
That game will suck you in.
But I think it's because it's giving, at least in my case,
some of the same feelings as when you're working on a program.
And you're just adding features and features to the program
and it's just a lot of fun and you keep going and going, you know?
It's the same kind of problem-solving.
It's fun.
It's one of those things that really just suck your time.
Inscription is like the only other game that had those wow moments,
like in Outer Wilds.
Yeah, Inscription is the next game I'm going to play after Bloodborne.
So, I put a poll on my channel in the community tab
and I put the games that I felt like playing.
Five of them.
And I was pretty torn between which one to play,
so I let the community choose.
And Inscription was the clear winner.
I don't think it's going to change
because Inscription is so far in the lead,
followed by Subnautica Below Zero, actually.
You should consider putting Sekito on that list.
Well, I've already played Sekito, Alexander M.
Played it, completed it, and loved it.
Super difficult, though.
But nowhere near as difficult as Rain World.
But the solid suggestion, nonetheless.
Great game.
All my programmer friends say Factorio is exactly like
what they do for work. Exactly, right?
So I'm not the only one who feel that way.
I'll put it up one more time. Hitman 1, 2, and 3.
Danny Dan, I've always wanted to play those.
But aren't there more than three?
I feel like I should start with the very first game,
which is like an older game at this point.
I actually do want to play Hitman.
I'm going to play... I don't have it on my list.
Let me actually put it...
Hitman series.
Yes, for sure.
I saw that they recently did something with Hitman 1, 2, and 3.
They all combined it into something, and people are praising it.
Saying, oh, this is great now.
Hey, frog! I'm sad I missed the stream,
but I'll be fun to watch back over all the progress you've made thus far.
I'm glad you're playing this. Good luck.
Thanks, frog. Yeah, it's been a blast.
I've had a lot of fun with this, as you can probably tell.
It's been going for five hours.
That's probably a big giveaway here.
Damn, Oliver, when are you going to play Out of Wiles?
I don't know, man. That game seems interesting, you know.
Maybe someday.
Hitman would be fun, yeah.
One of my favorite streamers...
His name was Three Dog.
He's like a Metal Gear Solid streamer.
I haven't actually watched any Metal Gear Solid, because I haven't played it yet.
But that's like his main thing, and he played a little bit of Hitman.
One of the 1, 2, or 3, I forget which one, and it looked super fun.
One of the newer ones he played.
I think the thing about Rain World's difficulty
is that bullshit plays an active, intentional role in the design,
since it's meant to simulate what it's like living in an ecosystem.
That's a fair... that's a fair point.
But it's definitely frustrating at times.
I can tell you that.
And I've seen multiple people in our community say the same,
that they actually quit the game because they couldn't deal with the bullshit.
You know?
If it wasn't for all the lore at the end of the tunnel there, you know?
I don't think I would have made it through either.
It's the lore that kept me going through those really dark moments.
But it was so worth it in the end.
Hey, Barry.
Just finished Minecraft, and I really enjoyed it.
There's Rain World now, but it's my first time joining the live,
so I dropped by to say hello world.
Hello, Barry.
Thanks for this 6.98 SGD.
I don't know what currency that is. Where are you from, Barry?
What is SGD?
Now I'm curious. I haven't seen that acronym.
But thank you. Thank you.
Wait a minute. Timu.
Isn't your name based on some kind of...
character in Dota?
Or is it League of Legends?
Or maybe I'm misremembering here.
Singapore. Oh, hello, Barry. Welcome.
Welcome, welcome.
Nice to have you.
Singaporean Dollar. Oh!
That makes sense.
SGD, Singaporean Dollar.
Cool.
Hadi the Holy Wolf.
$50.
Wow, thank you so much.
Hope your Terraria experience has been pleasant so far.
It's been amazing so far, Hadi.
I don't know if you've seen the stream or if you just joined,
but I've been having a blast with this game.
It's super fun.
I especially... you know what I love the most?
Today, in this game is...
when I found that maze.
The maze on a string.
It's the best way. You know the one you swing?
That was such a great,
progressional upgrade.
And God, it felt good to get that item.
You know, when I got that item,
the game was sort of like...
that's when it sort of clicked for me a little.
I was like, okay, okay, okay, here we go.
You know? Thank you so much, Hadi.
That's very generous of you.
Milano chocolate.
Is that a Discord icon with...
I can't even tell from here. It's so small.
But like one of those meme eyes, I don't know.
Thanks for the dollar, man.
Thank you so much.
It's a regular Finnish name.
Oh, shit, really?
Teemo.
Oh, I see.
But I get that often?
Oh, okay. That makes me feel better.
I'm sorry, Teemo.
I'm just curious here now.
So you're from Finland, right?
Has the average Finlandian
or Finnish person heard of Serral?
I'm not going to say more.
Does that name ring any bells to you at all?
Is he sort of famous in your country?
Serral?
Serral, maybe the way you pronounce it?
I'm not sure.
Probably not.
Because that's what I think of when I hear Finland lately.
Isn't Serral the Starcraft 2 pro?
Yes, he is.
He's probably the best player in the world at Starcraft 2.
Even better than the Koreans.
He's amazing.
I've been following him for so many years
and it's just a pleasure.
However, if you stream for 10 more minutes,
the length will be 6 hours including the timer and downtime though.
Actually, you're right.
Is that a record for me then?
Here's the crazy thing.
I know people on Twitch stream like 10 hours every day.
How the fuck do you do that?
That's insane.
I feel like...
I got sucked into the game right now, right?
And I forgot about time.
But 6 hours is quite a long time, isn't it?
My main association with Finland is Control.
Oh, it's the Finnish company that made that.
Cool.
I heard Serral was legendary years.
And he's so nonchalant about it too.
It's really nice.
He wins the entire tournament and drops a single map
and then stands on the podium and is like,
yeah, it was very good.
I played well.
Thanks, guys. And then he's off, you know?
I love him.
It's so cool.
How about a 24-hour stream?
If that has to happen, there would be breaks, I guess.
Eating breaks and bio breaks and all that.
In fact, I'm surprised I didn't need to go to the bathroom once during this.
This is very unusual for me.
Very unusual.
Kukukatsu, I love your name.
I just love that name, Kukukatsu.
Or maybe I pronounced it wrong.
Some people stream themselves sleeping though I've heard.
Yeah, I've heard about that too.
You have the guys behind Max Payne.
I've actually never played that.
It's an old game, isn't it?
By the way, Oliver, you might want to check out Noida.
I know Noida is made by Finnish people too.
And Noida is on my list for sure.
It was actually a bit...
I was questioning whether to do Noida or Terraria this time around for streams.
So it was actually between those two.
I have a question. Who wrote the short description for this stream?
I've been wondering for the whole stream.
Just AI.
Because I usually don't know what to write there.
So I just go to chat cheaply and be like...
Write a short summary of Terraria or something.
And then it does it, and I usually write it without spoilers, you know?
So it tries to make it as vague as possible.
And that's just what I put in.
It's just for people who don't know about...
What the game is about, you know?
But I guess I could also just go on Steam and copy-paste the description there.
That would probably be easier.
AI description.
In fact, guys, this whole stream has been AI. I'm so sorry.
I'm not even real, dude.
This has been brought to you by the power of artificial intelligence.
Nah, I feel like an AI wouldn't struggle that much in the beginning of the game.
That's... yeah.
AI Oliver's sad face.
You could include some instructions for no back-seeding or stuff in the description, too.
Guys, I feel like it's not even necessary. You guys have been awesome.
Nobody's spoiling anything in the chat.
And I mean, I'm not looking at the chat while I'm playing.
I feel like, and if there's any spoilers at all, there's usually a mod that will take care of it.
It's... I don't know. I feel like we have such a great community here.
People... people just know.
It's awesome.
But yeah, I should probably write a little sentence there just saying, you know?
You are strongly self-moderating.
And it's awesome.
Yeah, but new viewers won't know to not back-seed. That's true.
Yeah, I should definitely throw in a short explanation there in the description.
But I actually found out recently that not a lot of people realize what back-seeding means.
So that's why I didn't put it in the title of this video like I did with Minecraft.
So many people always ask, what does back-seeding mean?
Or maybe they have different interpretations of what constitutes back-seeding.
Aorta, they're not looking at chat during game. It's such a cool way of doing it.
We get all the spoilers out of our system when you're not looking.
Yeah, and I think it's sort of funny knowing that you guys are arguing between yourselves or...
Yeah, I don't know. It's like watching...
So I don't watch football, but I can imagine.
This is how it is. People sit down on a couch and watch football and they're just like,
Come on, you asshole! Fucking get the ball in there, you know?
Same kind of energy, I imagine. In a weird way.
And that just sounds fun.
You should have a giant red alarm siren pop up.
Don't back-seed!
I don't know about that.
Oh, the chaos in chat at times, Alexander?
He's exactly like that, Oliver.
That's awesome, Ghost. That's what I expect.
More supportive, but yeah, pretty much.
Okay, that's nice. I mean, you can say whatever you want.
I mean, it's all fun.
Come on, Oliver, put the door down!
The door! No, the door!
You get an in-game back-seater in this game, though. Damn, Joe.
I like Joe. You can't knock on Joe. Joe is great.
30 more minutes and this will be the longest stream so far.
Oh, really? So I have done more than this before.
I wonder which game that was. Must have been Minecraft.
It could also be Rain World. I did one long stream, I remember.
Just caught up with everything I missed. Hey, Obesity, how you doing?
There's something about your name, Obesity, and then just random picture of Mario.
It's just funny to me.
Diego, how you doing? Chat telepathy?
What do you mean? That one Minecraft stream was weirdly long.
Oh, okay, yeah. Oh, that was probably the New Year's stream, wasn't it?
Where I was drinking. Yeah, I totally forgot time in that one.
Justice for Maxwell.
Well, I mean, what happened to it?
Some new guy just came in and replaced Maxwell and now his name was Joe.
That was very odd. I thought he would just respawn.
I mean, he did, I guess, but as a reincarnated new person.
It was a bit weird. Big Mario.
He doesn't know about chat telepathy?
What is that? Or don't tell me.
No, don't tell him. Okay, maybe don't tell me then.
I don't know what it is. He does not know what that is and it's not supposed to.
Okay, you know what? It's my cue to get out of here anyway.
Guys, thank you so much for watching. This has been a goddamn blast!
I had so much fun with this. And it's cool to know that so many people enjoyed watching this, too.
So, I say to you now,
enjoy your Easter Day
or the rest of it, depending on where you are.
And yeah, I'm gonna be out of here. I'll be playing this game again soon.
Thanks for watching. You guys are the best.
Join the Discord. Hang out with the people.
And I'll see you around, okay? Have a good one! Adios!